<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Egg Recipes</title>
    <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Egg Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 08:25:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bibiresep.web.app/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Prepare Perfect Ayam bumbu bali</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/9-simple-way-to-prepare-perfect-ayam-bumbu-bali/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 08:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/9-simple-way-to-prepare-perfect-ayam-bumbu-bali/</guid>
      <description>Ayam bumbu bali
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s Brad, welcome to my recipe site. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a special dish, ayam bumbu bali. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Lihat juga resep Ayam Tahu Bumbu Bali enak lainnya. Tutorial cara membuat ayam bumbu bali,jangan lupa like komen share dan subscribe semoga bermanfaat,dan berikut ini Resep ayam bumbu bali Bahan bahan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps to Prepare Any-night-of-the-week Ayam Goreng</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/118-steps-to-prepare-any-night-of-the-week-ayam-goreng/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 19:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/118-steps-to-prepare-any-night-of-the-week-ayam-goreng/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Goreng
Hey everyone, it is Jim, welcome to our recipe page. Today, I will show you a way to make a distinctive dish, ayam goreng. One of my favorites food recipes. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Ayam Bahbas menyediakan Ayam Goreng dengan lima pilihan rasa yang siap membuat kamu Ini dia restoran Ayam Goreng enak di Jakarta yang legendaris banget dan sudah punya cabang di.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Make Any-night-of-the-week Ayam tahu bumbu lengket</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/6-simple-way-to-make-any-night-of-the-week-ayam-tahu-bumbu-lengket/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 18:07:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/6-simple-way-to-make-any-night-of-the-week-ayam-tahu-bumbu-lengket/</guid>
      <description>Ayam tahu bumbu lengket
Hello everybody, it is Louise, welcome to my recipe site. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a distinctive dish, ayam tahu bumbu lengket. One of my favorites. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Resep Ayam Bumbu Rujak - Kini, sudah banyak variasi makanan yang diolah dari ayam, salah satunya adalah ayam bumbu rujak. Rujak yang biasanya dipadukan dengan buah-buahan dan sayuran, bumbunya yang lezat kini sudah dipadukan dengan lauk sejuta umat, yaitu ayam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Ultimate Soto Ayam</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/131-how-to-make-ultimate-soto-ayam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 16:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/131-how-to-make-ultimate-soto-ayam/</guid>
      <description>Soto Ayam
Hello everybody, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an incredible day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a distinctive dish, soto ayam. One of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I will make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Lihat juga resep Soto Ayam/Ceker plus Kentang Crispy enak lainnya. Soto ayam merupakan satu dari ratusan ribu kuliner yang ada di Indonesia. Pada dasarnya soto ayam merupakan makanan yang berkuah kuning dengan suwiran ayam di dalamnya.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Prepare Super Quick Homemade Pad Krawpaw Gai Nasi Ayam Basil Thailand</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/173-simple-way-to-prepare-super-quick-homemade-pad-krawpaw-gai-nasi-ayam-basil-thailand/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 01:50:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/173-simple-way-to-prepare-super-quick-homemade-pad-krawpaw-gai-nasi-ayam-basil-thailand/</guid>
      <description>Pad Krawpaw Gai Nasi Ayam Basil Thailand
Hello everybody, I hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a special dish, pad krawpaw gai nasi ayam basil thailand. It is one of my favorites. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Pad Krawpaw Gai Nasi Ayam Basil Thailand is one of the most favored of recent trending meals in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps to Prepare Any-night-of-the-week Siomay ayam</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/8-steps-to-prepare-any-night-of-the-week-siomay-ayam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 19:23:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/8-steps-to-prepare-any-night-of-the-week-siomay-ayam/</guid>
      <description>Siomay ayam
Hey everyone, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an amazing day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a special dish, siomay ayam. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I am going to make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Siomay ayam is one of the most popular of recent trending meals in the world. It&amp;rsquo;s easy, it&amp;rsquo;s quick, it tastes delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Prepare Homemade Cilok ayam kuah</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/66-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-homemade-cilok-ayam-kuah/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2020 17:11:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/66-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-homemade-cilok-ayam-kuah/</guid>
      <description>Cilok ayam kuah
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s John, welcome to my recipe page. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a special dish, cilok ayam kuah. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Lada Bubuk. - Cilok Kuah Ayam* Namanya CILOK. KUAH AYAM, salah satu variasi dari Cilok. Resep Cilok Pedas Isi Ayam, Enak, Pedas dan Kenyalnya Pas!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easiest Way to Make Favorite Sate Ayam Manis</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/99-easiest-way-to-make-favorite-sate-ayam-manis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2020 08:39:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/99-easiest-way-to-make-favorite-sate-ayam-manis/</guid>
      <description>Sate Ayam Manis
Hello everybody, hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a special dish, sate ayam manis. It is one of my favorites. For mine, I am going to make it a little bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Resep sate ayam manis ini bisa jadikan alternatif lho buat kamu yang gak doyan dengan sate daging kambing. Dijamin deh rasanya bikin kamu gak mau berhenti makan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Prepare Super Quick Homemade Ayam Woku Kemangi</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/128-simple-way-to-prepare-super-quick-homemade-ayam-woku-kemangi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 13:17:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/128-simple-way-to-prepare-super-quick-homemade-ayam-woku-kemangi/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Woku Kemangi
Hey everyone, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an amazing day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a special dish, ayam woku kemangi. One of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I am going to make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Lihat juga resep Ayam woku kemanggi enak lainnya. Ayam woku biasanya dimasak hingga kuahnya mengental dan sedikit menyusut. Sajian ini adalah lauk yang sangat cocok bersanding dengan nasi putih panas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Ultimate Ayam panggang bumbu rujak no santan</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/170-recipe-of-ultimate-ayam-panggang-bumbu-rujak-no-santan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 09:51:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/170-recipe-of-ultimate-ayam-panggang-bumbu-rujak-no-santan/</guid>
      <description>Ayam panggang bumbu rujak no santan
Hello everybody, it is Drew, welcome to my recipe page. Today, I will show you a way to make a distinctive dish, ayam panggang bumbu rujak no santan. One of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Ayam panggang bumbu rujak no santan is one of the most popular of current trending meals on earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Award-winning Soto ayam kuah bening</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/95-recipe-of-award-winning-soto-ayam-kuah-bening/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 03:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/95-recipe-of-award-winning-soto-ayam-kuah-bening/</guid>
      <description>Soto ayam kuah bening
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s Brad, welcome to my recipe page. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a distinctive dish, soto ayam kuah bening. One of my favorites. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Soto ayam kuah bening is one of the most well liked of current trending foods on earth. It&amp;rsquo;s appreciated by millions every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easiest Way to Make Any-night-of-the-week Nasi Ayam Suir Pedas (Rice Bowl)</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/163-easiest-way-to-make-any-night-of-the-week-nasi-ayam-suir-pedas-rice-bowl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 05:51:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/163-easiest-way-to-make-any-night-of-the-week-nasi-ayam-suir-pedas-rice-bowl/</guid>
      <description>Nasi Ayam Suir Pedas (Rice Bowl)
Hey everyone, it is John, welcome to my recipe page. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a distinctive dish, nasi ayam suir pedas (rice bowl). One of my favorites. This time, I will make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Nasi Ayam Suir Pedas (Rice Bowl) is one of the most popular of current trending foods in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Make Favorite Ayam ungkep</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/75-step-by-step-guide-to-make-favorite-ayam-ungkep/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 01:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/75-step-by-step-guide-to-make-favorite-ayam-ungkep/</guid>
      <description>Ayam ungkep
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s Louise, welcome to our recipe page. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a special dish, ayam ungkep. One of my favorites food recipes. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Ayam ungkep is one of the most popular of current trending foods in the world. It is appreciated by millions daily. It&amp;rsquo;s easy, it&amp;rsquo;s fast, it tastes delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Super Quick Homemade Ayam Sisit Bali</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/7-recipe-of-super-quick-homemade-ayam-sisit-bali/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 22:57:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/7-recipe-of-super-quick-homemade-ayam-sisit-bali/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Sisit Bali
Hey everyone, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an incredible day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a special dish, ayam sisit bali. One of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Ayam Sisit Bali is one of the most popular of recent trending foods in the world. It&amp;rsquo;s easy, it&amp;rsquo;s fast, it tastes yummy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easiest Way to Make Homemade Ayam Kuah Pedas Simple</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/91-easiest-way-to-make-homemade-ayam-kuah-pedas-simple/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 22:50:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/91-easiest-way-to-make-homemade-ayam-kuah-pedas-simple/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Kuah Pedas Simple
Hey everyone, hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, I will show you a way to make a special dish, ayam kuah pedas simple. One of my favorites food recipes. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Ayam Kuah Pedas Simple is one of the most popular of current trending foods on earth. It is easy, it is quick, it tastes delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Any-night-of-the-week Ayam ungkep</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/82-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-ayam-ungkep/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 05:28:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/82-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-ayam-ungkep/</guid>
      <description>Ayam ungkep
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s Jim, welcome to my recipe site. Today, I will show you a way to make a special dish, ayam ungkep. It is one of my favorites. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Selain ayam goreng, ayam ungkep ini bisa diolah menjadi aneka resep lainnya, lho. Misalnya semur ayam, kalio ayam, dan rendang ayam. Mengedepankan aroma rempah-rempah, ayam ungkep jadi salah satu jenis masakan populer Indonesia lho.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Any-night-of-the-week Ayam Kecap Gurih</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/13-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-ayam-kecap-gurih/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 07:28:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/13-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-ayam-kecap-gurih/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Kecap Gurih
Hello everybody, hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an amazing day today. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a special dish, ayam kecap gurih. One of my favorites. This time, I am going to make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Ayam Kecap Gurih is one of the most favored of current trending foods on earth. It&amp;rsquo;s simple, it is fast, it tastes delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Super Quick Homemade Ayam Suwir Gurih Pedas</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/171-recipe-of-super-quick-homemade-ayam-suwir-gurih-pedas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 04:59:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/171-recipe-of-super-quick-homemade-ayam-suwir-gurih-pedas/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Suwir Gurih Pedas
Hey everyone, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an incredible day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a special dish, ayam suwir gurih pedas. It is one of my favorites. For mine, I will make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Assalamualaikum Selamat Datang di chanel Dapur Tomat Ceri Masak sederhana, praktis dan nikmat Kali ini mama mau masak nasi bakar ayam suwir kemangi pedas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easiest Way to Prepare Quick Soto Ayam</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/150-easiest-way-to-prepare-quick-soto-ayam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 00:19:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/150-easiest-way-to-prepare-quick-soto-ayam/</guid>
      <description>Soto Ayam
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s John, welcome to my recipe page. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a special dish, soto ayam. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Lihat juga resep Soto Ayam/Ceker plus Kentang Crispy enak lainnya. Soto ayam merupakan satu dari ratusan ribu kuliner yang ada di Indonesia. Pada dasarnya soto ayam merupakan makanan yang berkuah kuning dengan suwiran ayam di dalamnya.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Award-winning Sate kulit ayam yakitori</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/46-recipe-of-award-winning-sate-kulit-ayam-yakitori/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 15:21:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/46-recipe-of-award-winning-sate-kulit-ayam-yakitori/</guid>
      <description>Sate kulit ayam yakitori
Hey everyone, hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a special dish, sate kulit ayam yakitori. It is one of my favorites. For mine, I am going to make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Sate kulit ayam yakitori is one of the most popular of current trending foods on earth. It is enjoyed by millions daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Quick 220. Nasi Bakar Ayam Kemangi</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/184-recipe-of-quick-220-nasi-bakar-ayam-kemangi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 21:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/184-recipe-of-quick-220-nasi-bakar-ayam-kemangi/</guid>
      <description>220. Nasi Bakar Ayam Kemangi
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s Jim, welcome to my recipe page. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a distinctive dish, 220. nasi bakar ayam kemangi. One of my favorites food recipes. This time, I will make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Nasi Bakar Ayam Kemangi is one of the most well liked of current trending foods on earth. It&amp;rsquo;s appreciated by millions daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easiest Way to Prepare Ultimate Kare Ayam Sayuran</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/3-easiest-way-to-prepare-ultimate-kare-ayam-sayuran/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 03:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/3-easiest-way-to-prepare-ultimate-kare-ayam-sayuran/</guid>
      <description>Kare Ayam Sayuran
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s John, welcome to my recipe site. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a distinctive dish, kare ayam sayuran. One of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I will make it a little bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Selamat pagi semuanya, apa kabar nih cookpaders? Assalammuslaikum.salam sejahtera untuk semua..daging ayam untuk hidangan lezat hari ini, cobalah memasak kari ayam sayuran. Daging ayam dimasak santan, dipadukan dengan berbagai bumbu dan rempah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Make Ultimate Bubur ayam teri keju</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/18-simple-way-to-make-ultimate-bubur-ayam-teri-keju/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 18:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/18-simple-way-to-make-ultimate-bubur-ayam-teri-keju/</guid>
      <description>Bubur ayam teri keju
Hello everybody, it is me again, Dan, welcome to my recipe page. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a distinctive dish, bubur ayam teri keju. It is one of my favorites. This time, I am going to make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Bubur ayam teri keju is one of the most well liked of current trending meals in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps to Make Speedy Tofu cah ayam cincang saus teriyaki</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/38-steps-to-make-speedy-tofu-cah-ayam-cincang-saus-teriyaki/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 09:07:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/38-steps-to-make-speedy-tofu-cah-ayam-cincang-saus-teriyaki/</guid>
      <description>Tofu cah ayam cincang saus teriyaki
Hello everybody, hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a distinctive dish, tofu cah ayam cincang saus teriyaki. One of my favorites. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Teriyaki merupakan saus khas Jepang yang memiliki cita rasa manis. Di Indonesia, saus ini merupakan salah satu saus digemari banyak orang. Lihat juga resep Ayam Tofu Saos Tiram enak lainnya.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Prepare Super Quick Homemade Dada Ayam Krispi</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/148-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-super-quick-homemade-dada-ayam-krispi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 01:19:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/148-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-super-quick-homemade-dada-ayam-krispi/</guid>
      <description>Dada Ayam Krispi
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s me again, Dan, welcome to our recipe site. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a special dish, dada ayam krispi. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I am going to make it a bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Dada Ayam Krispi is one of the most favored of current trending foods on earth. It&amp;rsquo;s enjoyed by millions every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Ultimate Sop Ceker Ayam</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/45-how-to-make-ultimate-sop-ceker-ayam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 05:46:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/45-how-to-make-ultimate-sop-ceker-ayam/</guid>
      <description>Sop Ceker Ayam
Hello everybody, hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an amazing day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a special dish, sop ceker ayam. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Resep Sop Ceker Ayam - Bagus Untuk Anak Kecil Yang penasaran sama muka Mama Bay Cek Video ini : https: https.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Prepare Super Quick Homemade Brindil ayam, topu asam manis</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/174-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-super-quick-homemade-brindil-ayam-topu-asam-manis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 02:18:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/174-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-super-quick-homemade-brindil-ayam-topu-asam-manis/</guid>
      <description>Brindil ayam, topu asam manis
Hey everyone, hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an amazing day today. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a special dish, brindil ayam, topu asam manis. It is one of my favorites. For mine, I will make it a little bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Brindil ayam, topu asam manis is one of the most well liked of current trending foods in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Make Speedy Tahu bakso ayam</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/56-step-by-step-guide-to-make-speedy-tahu-bakso-ayam/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 06:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/56-step-by-step-guide-to-make-speedy-tahu-bakso-ayam/</guid>
      <description>Tahu bakso ayam
Hey everyone, it is Brad, welcome to our recipe site. Today, I will show you a way to make a distinctive dish, tahu bakso ayam. One of my favorites. This time, I will make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Tahu bakso ayam is one of the most favored of recent trending foods in the world. It is easy, it is fast, it tastes yummy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Homemade Ayam Panggang Pedas Manis</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/78-recipe-of-homemade-ayam-panggang-pedas-manis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 09:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/78-recipe-of-homemade-ayam-panggang-pedas-manis/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Panggang Pedas Manis
Hey everyone, hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a distinctive dish, ayam panggang pedas manis. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I am going to make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Ayam Panggang Pedas Manis is one of the most well liked of recent trending foods in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Make Award-winning Soto ayam</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/124-simple-way-to-make-award-winning-soto-ayam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 21:53:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/124-simple-way-to-make-award-winning-soto-ayam/</guid>
      <description>Soto ayam
Hey everyone, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an amazing day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a distinctive dish, soto ayam. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I am going to make it a bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Soto ayam is one of the most popular of current trending foods in the world. It&amp;rsquo;s simple, it is fast, it tastes delicious. It&amp;rsquo;s enjoyed by millions every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Make Favorite Sup Ayam Bakso</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/127-step-by-step-guide-to-make-favorite-sup-ayam-bakso/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 02:19:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/127-step-by-step-guide-to-make-favorite-sup-ayam-bakso/</guid>
      <description>Sup Ayam Bakso
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s John, welcome to our recipe site. Today, I will show you a way to make a special dish, sup ayam bakso. It is one of my favorites. This time, I am going to make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Kenapa sop ini dinamakan Sup Mutiara bakso? Sup ayam bakso jamur. foto: Instagram/@linietanaya. Mulai dari Bakso Sapi, Ayam, Ikan, Cara Membuat Resep Bakso - Makanan khas Indonesia yang tak kalah populer dengan makanan luar negeri iakah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Prepare Speedy Sempolan ayam</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/89-how-to-prepare-speedy-sempolan-ayam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 23:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/89-how-to-prepare-speedy-sempolan-ayam/</guid>
      <description>Sempolan ayam
Hello everybody, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an incredible day today. Today, I will show you a way to make a distinctive dish, sempolan ayam. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I am going to make it a bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Sempolan ayam is one of the most well liked of recent trending meals on earth. It&amp;rsquo;s enjoyed by millions every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps to Prepare Homemade Sop ayam kembang tahu</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/77-steps-to-prepare-homemade-sop-ayam-kembang-tahu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 19:35:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/77-steps-to-prepare-homemade-sop-ayam-kembang-tahu/</guid>
      <description>Sop ayam kembang tahu
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s me again, Dan, welcome to my recipe page. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a special dish, sop ayam kembang tahu. It is one of my favorites. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Sop ayam kembang tahu is one of the most well liked of current trending foods in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Any-night-of-the-week Angsio ceker ayam</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/31-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-angsio-ceker-ayam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 05:49:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/31-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-angsio-ceker-ayam/</guid>
      <description>Angsio ceker ayam
Hello everybody, hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, I will show you a way to make a distinctive dish, angsio ceker ayam. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I will make it a little bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Angsio ceker ayam adalah salah satu kuliner atau masakan khas Cina. Angsio dalam bahasa Cina artinya setelah direbus menjadi merah, memasak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Prepare Favorite Roti Goreng Isi Ayam</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/144-how-to-prepare-favorite-roti-goreng-isi-ayam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 01:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/144-how-to-prepare-favorite-roti-goreng-isi-ayam/</guid>
      <description>Roti Goreng Isi Ayam
Hey everyone, I hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a special dish, roti goreng isi ayam. One of my favorites. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Roti Goreng Isi Ayam is one of the most popular of current trending meals in the world. It&amp;rsquo;s simple, it&amp;rsquo;s quick, it tastes delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Make Favorite Opor Ayam Kuah Putih (Ayam Kampung Bakar)</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/54-simple-way-to-make-favorite-opor-ayam-kuah-putih-ayam-kampung-bakar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 16:45:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/54-simple-way-to-make-favorite-opor-ayam-kuah-putih-ayam-kampung-bakar/</guid>
      <description>Opor Ayam Kuah Putih (Ayam Kampung Bakar)
Hey everyone, it is me, Dave, welcome to my recipe site. Today, I will show you a way to make a distinctive dish, opor ayam kuah putih (ayam kampung bakar). One of my favorites food recipes. This time, I am going to make it a little bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Opor ayam merupakan salah satu menu yang wajib ada ketika Lebaran.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Award-winning Sate ayam,lontong bumbu kacang</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/28-recipe-of-award-winning-sate-ayam-lontong-bumbu-kacang/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 17:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/28-recipe-of-award-winning-sate-ayam-lontong-bumbu-kacang/</guid>
      <description>Sate ayam,lontong bumbu kacang
Hey everyone, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an amazing day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a special dish, sate ayam,lontong bumbu kacang. One of my favorites. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Sate ayam,lontong bumbu kacang is one of the most well liked of recent trending meals in the world. It is enjoyed by millions daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps to Prepare Quick Ayam KULUYUK (Asam manis)</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/145-steps-to-prepare-quick-ayam-kuluyuk-asam-manis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 20:21:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/145-steps-to-prepare-quick-ayam-kuluyuk-asam-manis/</guid>
      <description>Ayam KULUYUK (Asam manis)
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s Drew, welcome to my recipe site. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a distinctive dish, ayam kuluyuk (asam manis). It is one of my favorites. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Resep andalan ibuqu kini aku share utk kalian. Resep simpel praktis dan ekonomis resep ayam kuluyuk atau bahasa kerennya sweet and sour chicken ini simpel sih tapi untuk rasa sangat nyuuuussss, selain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps to Prepare Favorite Sempol ayam...😋😍</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/105-steps-to-prepare-favorite-sempol-ayam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 07:48:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/105-steps-to-prepare-favorite-sempol-ayam/</guid>
      <description>Sempol ayam&amp;amp;hellip;😋😍
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s Jim, welcome to my recipe page. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a special dish, sempol ayam&amp;hellip;😋😍. One of my favorites. This time, I am going to make it a little bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Kalau di Malang anda temukan sempol ayam versi mini-mini dengan tusukan sate. Nah, kalau anda buat sendiri, boleh dong dibuat lebih besar? Resep Sempol Ayam - Aneka jajanantanah air kini semakin beragam dan makin banyak jenisnya karena telah dimodifikasi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps to Prepare Favorite Pangsit Goreng isi Ayam Udang</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/65-steps-to-prepare-favorite-pangsit-goreng-isi-ayam-udang/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 07:44:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/65-steps-to-prepare-favorite-pangsit-goreng-isi-ayam-udang/</guid>
      <description>Pangsit Goreng isi Ayam Udang
Hello everybody, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an amazing day today. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a distinctive dish, pangsit goreng isi ayam udang. One of my favorites food recipes. This time, I am going to make it a little bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Pangsit goreng sering disajikan bersama mie ayam atau bakso. Moms bisa membuatnya di rumah Isi kulit pangsit dengan campuran udang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resep Chocolate plate banana sandwich Anti Gagal</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/3-resep-chocolate-plate-banana-sandwich-anti-gagal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 13:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/3-resep-chocolate-plate-banana-sandwich-anti-gagal/</guid>
      <description>Chocolate plate banana sandwich
Sedang mencari inspirasi resep chocolate plate banana sandwich yang unik? Cara menyiapkannya memang susah-susah gampang. Kalau salah mengolah maka hasilnya tidak akan memuaskan dan justru cenderung tidak enak. Padahal chocolate plate banana sandwich yang enak harusnya sih punya aroma dan rasa yang dapat memancing selera kita.
Ada beberapa hal yang sedikit banyak mempengaruhi kualitas rasa dari chocolate plate banana sandwich, pertama dari jenis bahan, kemudian pemilihan bahan segar, sampai cara membuat dan menghidangkannya.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easiest Way to Prepare Favorite Mie ayam homemade</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/168-easiest-way-to-prepare-favorite-mie-ayam-homemade/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 12:46:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/168-easiest-way-to-prepare-favorite-mie-ayam-homemade/</guid>
      <description>Mie ayam homemade
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s Jim, welcome to our recipe page. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a special dish, mie ayam homemade. It is one of my favorites. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Mie ayam homemade is one of the most well liked of current trending meals in the world. It is simple, it is fast, it tastes yummy. It is enjoyed by millions every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Prepare Speedy Ayam Suwir Bumbu Bali</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/157-how-to-prepare-speedy-ayam-suwir-bumbu-bali/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 05:38:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/157-how-to-prepare-speedy-ayam-suwir-bumbu-bali/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Suwir Bumbu Bali
Hello everybody, hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an incredible day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a distinctive dish, ayam suwir bumbu bali. One of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I will make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Ayam Suwir Bumbu Bali is one of the most popular of current trending foods in the world. It is enjoyed by millions daily. It is easy, it&amp;rsquo;s quick, it tastes delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Make Any-night-of-the-week Ayam Masak Sambal Ijo</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/111-simple-way-to-make-any-night-of-the-week-ayam-masak-sambal-ijo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 08:22:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/111-simple-way-to-make-any-night-of-the-week-ayam-masak-sambal-ijo/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Masak Sambal Ijo
Hey everyone, it is John, welcome to my recipe page. Today, I will show you a way to make a distinctive dish, ayam masak sambal ijo. It is one of my favorites. For mine, I will make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Cara Memasak Ayam Masak Sambal Hijau. Gaulkan ayam dengan serbuk kunyit dan sedikit garam. Kemudian goreng ayam hingga masak atau hampir masak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Prepare Favorite 395. Ayam Kecap Sunda</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/96-how-to-prepare-favorite-395-ayam-kecap-sunda/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 15:42:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/96-how-to-prepare-favorite-395-ayam-kecap-sunda/</guid>
      <description>395. Ayam Kecap Sunda
Hey everyone, it is Drew, welcome to my recipe site. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a special dish, 395. ayam kecap sunda. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Ada yang pernah coba dan suka sama ayam kecap sunda ini? cobain yuk bun. Resep asli dari Chef Yongki Gunawan tapi takarannya saya sesuaikan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Make Super Quick Homemade Ayam Goreng Bumbu Ungkep</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/169-step-by-step-guide-to-make-super-quick-homemade-ayam-goreng-bumbu-ungkep/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 09:44:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/169-step-by-step-guide-to-make-super-quick-homemade-ayam-goreng-bumbu-ungkep/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Goreng Bumbu Ungkep
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s me, Dave, welcome to my recipe page. Today, I will show you a way to make a distinctive dish, ayam goreng bumbu ungkep. It is one of my favorites. This time, I am going to make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Ayam Goreng Empuk, Gurih dan Bumbu Meresap. Rahasia membuat ayam ungkep bumbu meresap ke dalam dan daging ayamnya lembut banget.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Prepare Favorite 528.Ayam Kentang Panggang</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/23-how-to-prepare-favorite-528ayam-kentang-panggang/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 04:19:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/23-how-to-prepare-favorite-528ayam-kentang-panggang/</guid>
      <description>528.Ayam Kentang Panggang
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s me again, Dan, welcome to my recipe site. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a distinctive dish, 528.ayam kentang panggang. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I will make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
528.Ayam Kentang Panggang is one of the most well liked of current trending foods on earth. It&amp;rsquo;s easy, it is fast, it tastes delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Prepare Favorite Semur Ayam &#43; Kentang</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/106-simple-way-to-prepare-favorite-semur-ayam-kentang/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 04:13:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/106-simple-way-to-prepare-favorite-semur-ayam-kentang/</guid>
      <description>Semur Ayam &amp;#43; Kentang
Hey everyone, it is Louise, welcome to our recipe page. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a special dish, semur ayam + kentang. One of my favorites. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Semur Ayam + Kentang is one of the most well liked of recent trending foods in the world. It&amp;rsquo;s enjoyed by millions daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Prepare Perfect Rica-Rica Ayam Kemangi</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/61-how-to-prepare-perfect-rica-rica-ayam-kemangi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 14:47:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/61-how-to-prepare-perfect-rica-rica-ayam-kemangi/</guid>
      <description>Rica-Rica Ayam Kemangi
Hey everyone, it is me, Dave, welcome to our recipe site. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a distinctive dish, rica-rica ayam kemangi. It is one of my favorites. This time, I will make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Ayam, bahan makanan yang sering kita temui sehari hari ini memang bisa dijadikan berbagai macam variasi masakan yang lezat mulai dari ayam kecap,ayam bakar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Make Perfect Day. 159 Nasi Sop dan Ati Ayam Goreng (11 month&#43;)</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/76-simple-way-to-make-perfect-day-159-nasi-sop-dan-ati-ayam-goreng-11-month/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 14:03:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/76-simple-way-to-make-perfect-day-159-nasi-sop-dan-ati-ayam-goreng-11-month/</guid>
      <description>Day. 159 Nasi Sop dan Ati Ayam Goreng (11 month&amp;#43;)
Hello everybody, hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a special dish, day. 159 nasi sop dan ati ayam goreng (11 month+). It is one of my favorites. This time, I am going to make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Penonton dan Subscriber chanel youtube Si Jum Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Prepare Ultimate Semur ayam kentang</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/109-simple-way-to-prepare-ultimate-semur-ayam-kentang/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 13:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/109-simple-way-to-prepare-ultimate-semur-ayam-kentang/</guid>
      <description>Semur ayam kentang
Hey everyone, hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an amazing day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a distinctive dish, semur ayam kentang. It is one of my favorites. For mine, I will make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Semur ayam kentang is one of the most popular of recent trending foods in the world. It&amp;rsquo;s easy, it&amp;rsquo;s quick, it tastes yummy. It&amp;rsquo;s enjoyed by millions daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Homemade Mie ayam rumahan</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/115-recipe-of-homemade-mie-ayam-rumahan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 00:52:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/115-recipe-of-homemade-mie-ayam-rumahan/</guid>
      <description>Mie ayam rumahan
Hello everybody, I hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a distinctive dish, mie ayam rumahan. One of my favorites food recipes. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Mie ayam rumahan is one of the most popular of current trending meals in the world. It&amp;rsquo;s simple, it&amp;rsquo;s fast, it tastes yummy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Make Quick Sop Ayam</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/29-step-by-step-guide-to-make-quick-sop-ayam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 11:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/29-step-by-step-guide-to-make-quick-sop-ayam/</guid>
      <description>Sop Ayam
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s Jim, welcome to my recipe page. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a special dish, sop ayam. It is one of my favorites. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Lihat juga resep Sup ayam shedapp enak lainnya. Resep Sup Ayam, Ikuti video masak cara membuat sup ayam nya step by step ya. Resep sop ayam mama lita pembawa kemenangan DI masterchef.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Make Any-night-of-the-week Ayam Masak Cabai Hijau</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/143-simple-way-to-make-any-night-of-the-week-ayam-masak-cabai-hijau/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 01:43:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/143-simple-way-to-make-any-night-of-the-week-ayam-masak-cabai-hijau/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Masak Cabai Hijau
Hello everybody, I hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a distinctive dish, ayam masak cabai hijau. It is one of my favorites. For mine, I am going to make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Ayam Masak Cabai Hijau is one of the most well liked of current trending meals in the world. It is appreciated by millions daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Make Perfect Ayam Panggang Lada Hitam dgn Salad dan Sambal Dabu-dabu</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/0-step-by-step-guide-to-make-perfect-ayam-panggang-lada-hitam-dgn-salad-dan-sambal-dabu-dabu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:41:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/0-step-by-step-guide-to-make-perfect-ayam-panggang-lada-hitam-dgn-salad-dan-sambal-dabu-dabu/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Panggang Lada Hitam dgn Salad dan Sambal Dabu-dabu
Hello everybody, it is me, Dave, welcome to my recipe site. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a special dish, ayam panggang lada hitam dgn salad dan sambal dabu-dabu. One of my favorites. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Lihat juga resep Ayam crispy sambal dabu dabu enak lainnya!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Make Quick Ayam bakar ketumbar</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/108-simple-way-to-make-quick-ayam-bakar-ketumbar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 21:33:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/108-simple-way-to-make-quick-ayam-bakar-ketumbar/</guid>
      <description>Ayam bakar ketumbar
Hello everybody, I hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a distinctive dish, ayam bakar ketumbar. One of my favorites. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Resep ayam bakar kecap praktis bumbu kuning ketumbar Assalamualaikum.wr. wb. ayam bakar kecap banyak sekali dijual dimana-mana.tapi kali ini ayam bakar. Ayam bakar ini bisa dijadikan menu makan sarapan, makan siang bahkan makan malam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Homemade Sup Ayam Pak Min Klaten</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/162-recipe-of-homemade-sup-ayam-pak-min-klaten/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2020 12:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/162-recipe-of-homemade-sup-ayam-pak-min-klaten/</guid>
      <description>Sup Ayam Pak Min Klaten
Hello everybody, I hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a distinctive dish, sup ayam pak min klaten. One of my favorites food recipes. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Cara Membuat : − Rebus Ayam Kampung bersama Bunga Lawang, Kapulaga, dan Pala sampai air berkurang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Prepare Favorite Sop Brenebone Ayam</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/154-how-to-prepare-favorite-sop-brenebone-ayam/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 09:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/154-how-to-prepare-favorite-sop-brenebone-ayam/</guid>
      <description>Sop Brenebone Ayam
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s me again, Dan, welcome to my recipe page. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a distinctive dish, sop brenebone ayam. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I am going to make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Resep Sup Ayam, Ikuti video masak cara membuat sup ayam nya step by step ya. Sop Ayam Bening Tanpa Santan Mantep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Super Quick Homemade Kare Ayam Sayuran</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/140-recipe-of-super-quick-homemade-kare-ayam-sayuran/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 02:37:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/140-recipe-of-super-quick-homemade-kare-ayam-sayuran/</guid>
      <description>Kare Ayam Sayuran
Hey everyone, it is Drew, welcome to our recipe page. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a special dish, kare ayam sayuran. One of my favorites food recipes. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Kare Ayam Sayuran is one of the most favored of current trending meals on earth. It&amp;rsquo;s easy, it&amp;rsquo;s quick, it tastes delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps to Prepare Homemade Mie Ayam Jamur</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/151-steps-to-prepare-homemade-mie-ayam-jamur/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 03:27:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/151-steps-to-prepare-homemade-mie-ayam-jamur/</guid>
      <description>Mie Ayam Jamur
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s Drew, welcome to our recipe site. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a special dish, mie ayam jamur. It is one of my favorites. For mine, I will make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Mie ayam jamur merupakan salah satu olahan mie yang sering ditemui, mulai dari penjual-penjual di pinggir jalan hingga di restoran-restoran. Tekstur mie yang lembut dan kenyal berpadu dengan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Prepare Speedy Ayam mentega masak oven</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/114-simple-way-to-prepare-speedy-ayam-mentega-masak-oven/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 02:52:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/114-simple-way-to-prepare-speedy-ayam-mentega-masak-oven/</guid>
      <description>Ayam mentega masak oven
Hello everybody, it is John, welcome to our recipe page. Today, I will show you a way to make a distinctive dish, ayam mentega masak oven. One of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Sajian ayam panggang madu oven adalah sajian yang enak dan lezat. Kali ini hidangan lezat ini tidak hanya akan dapat anda santap di restoran atau rumah makan tempat biasa anda mengunjugi saat hasrat lapar melanda.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resep Bolu coklat mirip brownies no mixer tetep enak Anti Gagal</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/1-resep-bolu-coklat-mirip-brownies-no-mixer-tetep-enak-anti-gagal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 05:19:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/1-resep-bolu-coklat-mirip-brownies-no-mixer-tetep-enak-anti-gagal/</guid>
      <description>Bolu coklat mirip brownies no mixer tetep enak
Lagi mencari inspirasi resep bolu coklat mirip brownies no mixer tetep enak yang unik? Cara membuatnya memang tidak susah dan tidak juga mudah. Jika keliru mengolah maka hasilnya akan hambar dan justru cenderung tidak enak. Padahal bolu coklat mirip brownies no mixer tetep enak yang enak seharusnya memiliki aroma dan cita rasa yang bisa memancing selera kita.
Banyak hal yang sedikit banyak berpengaruh terhadap kualitas rasa dari bolu coklat mirip brownies no mixer tetep enak, mulai dari jenis bahan, selanjutnya pemilihan bahan segar, hingga cara membuat dan menyajikannya.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps to Prepare Homemade Tongseng daging ayam</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/156-steps-to-prepare-homemade-tongseng-daging-ayam/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 05:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/156-steps-to-prepare-homemade-tongseng-daging-ayam/</guid>
      <description>Tongseng daging ayam
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s me, Dave, welcome to my recipe page. Today, I will show you a way to make a distinctive dish, tongseng daging ayam. One of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Tongseng daging ayam is one of the most favored of recent trending foods in the world. It&amp;rsquo;s enjoyed by millions every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Prepare Award-winning Ayam Balado</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/155-how-to-prepare-award-winning-ayam-balado/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 15:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/155-how-to-prepare-award-winning-ayam-balado/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Balado
Hey everyone, I hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a distinctive dish, ayam balado. It is one of my favorites. This time, I will make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Lihat juga resep Balado Rempela Ati Ayam ala Aku enak lainnya. ayam balado, ayam balado asli minang, ayam balado pete, ayam bumbu pete, balado chicken, chili fried chicken, masakan RESEP AYAM BALADO PADANG, Resep Masakan Indonesia Sehari-hari.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Prepare Super Quick Homemade Ayam geprek runahan</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/120-simple-way-to-prepare-super-quick-homemade-ayam-geprek-runahan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 12:59:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/120-simple-way-to-prepare-super-quick-homemade-ayam-geprek-runahan/</guid>
      <description>Ayam geprek runahan
Hello everybody, I hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a distinctive dish, ayam geprek runahan. One of my favorites food recipes. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Ayam geprek runahan is one of the most popular of current trending meals on earth. It is simple, it is quick, it tastes yummy. It is enjoyed by millions daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Super Quick Homemade Mie goreng cap 3 ayam</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/139-recipe-of-super-quick-homemade-mie-goreng-cap-3-ayam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 04:56:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/139-recipe-of-super-quick-homemade-mie-goreng-cap-3-ayam/</guid>
      <description>Mie goreng cap 3 ayam
Hello everybody, it is John, welcome to our recipe site. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a special dish, mie goreng cap 3 ayam. It is one of my favorites. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Mie goreng cap 3 ayam is one of the most popular of recent trending meals on earth. It&amp;rsquo;s easy, it&amp;rsquo;s quick, it tastes yummy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps to Make Perfect *mie ayam bumbu rujak,no santan*</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/68-steps-to-make-perfect-mie-ayam-bumbu-rujak-no-santan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 10:34:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/68-steps-to-make-perfect-mie-ayam-bumbu-rujak-no-santan/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;mie ayam bumbu rujak,no santan&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;
Hey everyone, it is me, Dave, welcome to our recipe site. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a distinctive dish, mie ayam bumbu rujak,no santan. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
mie ayam bumbu rujak,no santan is one of the most popular of recent trending foods on earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Prepare Super Quick Homemade Ceker Ayam Rebus Tips</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/16-simple-way-to-prepare-super-quick-homemade-ceker-ayam-rebus-tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2020 01:12:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/16-simple-way-to-prepare-super-quick-homemade-ceker-ayam-rebus-tips/</guid>
      <description>Ceker Ayam Rebus Tips
Hello everybody, I hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a distinctive dish, ceker ayam rebus tips. One of my favorites food recipes. This time, I will make it a little bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Kali ini saya berbagi Tips Cara Rebus Ceker Ayam [ JADI EMPUK + TIDAK BAU AMIS ] Bagi kalian yang suka dengan olahan ceker, sebelum di masak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easiest Way to Make Super Quick Homemade Soto ayam</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/165-easiest-way-to-make-super-quick-homemade-soto-ayam/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 02:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/165-easiest-way-to-make-super-quick-homemade-soto-ayam/</guid>
      <description>Soto ayam
Hey everyone, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an incredible day today. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a distinctive dish, soto ayam. It is one of my favorites. For mine, I will make it a little bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Lihat juga resep Soto Ayam/Ceker plus Kentang Crispy enak lainnya. Soto ayam merupakan satu dari ratusan ribu kuliner yang ada di Indonesia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Prepare Homemade Kare Ayam Mix Sayur</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/51-simple-way-to-prepare-homemade-kare-ayam-mix-sayur/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 07:01:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/51-simple-way-to-prepare-homemade-kare-ayam-mix-sayur/</guid>
      <description>Kare Ayam Mix Sayur
Hey everyone, I hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a distinctive dish, kare ayam mix sayur. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
MasyaAllah Tabarakallah Channel ini berisi tentang kegemaran saya. Kali ini aku kasih resep yg spesial kare ayam Jawa, hampir kalau ada acara menu satu ini tidak pernah ketinggalan utk dihidangkan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Make Ultimate Nasi ayam bon cabe</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/152-step-by-step-guide-to-make-ultimate-nasi-ayam-bon-cabe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 08:23:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/152-step-by-step-guide-to-make-ultimate-nasi-ayam-bon-cabe/</guid>
      <description>Nasi ayam bon cabe
Hey everyone, I hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a special dish, nasi ayam bon cabe. One of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I will make it a little bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Nasi ayam bon cabe is one of the most popular of recent trending meals on earth. It is easy, it is fast, it tastes yummy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Quick Buntil daun pepaya isi ayam</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/134-recipe-of-quick-buntil-daun-pepaya-isi-ayam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 06:41:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/134-recipe-of-quick-buntil-daun-pepaya-isi-ayam/</guid>
      <description>Buntil daun pepaya isi ayam
Hey everyone, hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an incredible day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a special dish, buntil daun pepaya isi ayam. It is one of my favorites. This time, I am going to make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Bahan dasar untuk membuat buntil ini menggunakan daun pepaya dan daun singkong. Namun, kali ini kita akan membuat masakan buntil daun pepaya.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Prepare Any-night-of-the-week Ayam Goreng Mentega</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/136-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-any-night-of-the-week-ayam-goreng-mentega/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/136-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-any-night-of-the-week-ayam-goreng-mentega/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Goreng Mentega
Hello everybody, hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a distinctive dish, ayam goreng mentega. It is one of my favorites. This time, I am going to make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Resep Ayam Goreng Mentega - Apabila kalian biasa memasak ayam goreng di minyak goreng Jadi ayam goreng mentega ini tidak hanya di goreng dengan menggunakan mentega sebagai.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Perfect Sayap ayam goreng</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/55-recipe-of-perfect-sayap-ayam-goreng/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 12:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/55-recipe-of-perfect-sayap-ayam-goreng/</guid>
      <description>Sayap ayam goreng
Hello everybody, it is me, Dave, welcome to my recipe page. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a special dish, sayap ayam goreng. One of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I am going to make it a little bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Selamat datang kembali di channel Saya, Heny Rosneyn Cooking &amp;amp; Culinary. Sayap Ayam Goreng Special, Rasa Krenyes Mantul Sangat sajian menu ayam itu sudah biasa dan simple kali ini aku mau menyajikan menu biasa tapi bisa menggugah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Speedy Ayam bakar pedas</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/113-recipe-of-speedy-ayam-bakar-pedas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 01:49:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/113-recipe-of-speedy-ayam-bakar-pedas/</guid>
      <description>Ayam bakar pedas
Hey everyone, it is John, welcome to our recipe page. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a distinctive dish, ayam bakar pedas. One of my favorites. This time, I am going to make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Begitupun caranya untuk resep ayam bakar kecap pedas manis ini yang seru banget untuk dicoba. Sajian ayam bakar bumbu pedas manis adalah hidangan yang enak dan lezat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Make Ultimate Ayam Kecap Pedas</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/137-simple-way-to-make-ultimate-ayam-kecap-pedas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 04:18:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/137-simple-way-to-make-ultimate-ayam-kecap-pedas/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Kecap Pedas
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s Brad, welcome to my recipe site. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a special dish, ayam kecap pedas. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I will make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Ayam kecap adalah salah satu lauk simpel yang sering hadir di meja makan keluarga nusantara. Ada juga yang lebih senang memadukan rasa manis ayam kecap dengan diperkaya rasa pedas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Super Quick Homemade Ayam Bakar Taliwang</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/98-recipe-of-super-quick-homemade-ayam-bakar-taliwang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 14:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/98-recipe-of-super-quick-homemade-ayam-bakar-taliwang/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Bakar Taliwang
Hey everyone, it is Brad, welcome to my recipe page. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a distinctive dish, ayam bakar taliwang. One of my favorites food recipes. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Cukup stock FROZEN PACK AYAM BAKAR TALIWANG BABA SAVANNA aja dirumah, diangetin, sambil ngebayangin makan dipinggir pantai atau di desa Sembalun sebelum pendakian gunung. Ayam Bakar Taliwang is a type of Indonesian grilled chicken originally from Lombok.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Ultimate Sup Chiceaso (Chikuwa, ceker ayam dan bakso)</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/52-how-to-make-ultimate-sup-chiceaso-chikuwa-ceker-ayam-dan-bakso/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 15:43:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/52-how-to-make-ultimate-sup-chiceaso-chikuwa-ceker-ayam-dan-bakso/</guid>
      <description>Sup Chiceaso (Chikuwa, ceker ayam dan bakso)
Hey everyone, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an amazing day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a special dish, sup chiceaso (chikuwa, ceker ayam dan bakso). One of my favorites food recipes. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Kesibukan para emak di jaman now sangat luar biasa.dari mengurus rumah ,masak buat suami dan anak dan bekerja.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Make Super Quick Homemade Somay Ayam</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/110-step-by-step-guide-to-make-super-quick-homemade-somay-ayam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 08:54:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/110-step-by-step-guide-to-make-super-quick-homemade-somay-ayam/</guid>
      <description>Somay Ayam
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s Drew, welcome to our recipe page. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a special dish, somay ayam. It is one of my favorites. This time, I will make it a bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Di video kali ini saya akan berbagi resep SOMAY AYAM UDANG. Rasanya enak dan bikinnya gampang banget. Resep Somay Ayam: Dari Siomay Sukasuka Untuk Anda.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Quick #Ayam ungkep bumbu kacang</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/39-recipe-of-quick-ayam-ungkep-bumbu-kacang/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 22:29:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/39-recipe-of-quick-ayam-ungkep-bumbu-kacang/</guid>
      <description>#Ayam ungkep bumbu kacang
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s John, welcome to my recipe page. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a special dish, #ayam ungkep bumbu kacang. It is one of my favorites. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
#Ayam ungkep bumbu kacang is one of the most popular of current trending meals in the world. It&amp;rsquo;s simple, it&amp;rsquo;s quick, it tastes yummy. It&amp;rsquo;s appreciated by millions every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Quick Pepes ayam magicom</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/141-recipe-of-quick-pepes-ayam-magicom/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 17:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/141-recipe-of-quick-pepes-ayam-magicom/</guid>
      <description>Pepes ayam magicom
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s Drew, welcome to my recipe site. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a distinctive dish, pepes ayam magicom. One of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I am going to make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Pepes ayam magicom is one of the most favored of recent trending foods in the world. It is appreciated by millions every day. It is simple, it&amp;rsquo;s fast, it tastes delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cara Gampang Membuat Brownies Kukus Siram Cokelat yang Enak</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/6-cara-gampang-membuat-brownies-kukus-siram-cokelat-yang-enak/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 23:18:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/6-cara-gampang-membuat-brownies-kukus-siram-cokelat-yang-enak/</guid>
      <description>Brownies Kukus Siram Cokelat
Anda sedang mencari inspirasi resep brownies kukus siram cokelat yang unik? Cara membuatnya memang susah-susah gampang. Kalau keliru mengolah maka hasilnya tidak akan memuaskan dan justru cenderung tidak enak. Padahal brownies kukus siram cokelat yang enak seharusnya mempunyai aroma dan cita rasa yang bisa memancing selera kita.
Brownies kukus iniiii Enak banget bikin Nagih hihihi Yukkk cobain di rumah. Jangan Lupa tekan tombol lonceng agar tidak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Ultimate Semur Ayam Betawi</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/161-recipe-of-ultimate-semur-ayam-betawi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 18:37:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/161-recipe-of-ultimate-semur-ayam-betawi/</guid>
      <description>Semur Ayam Betawi
Hey everyone, hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a special dish, semur ayam betawi. One of my favorites. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Semur Ayam Betawi is one of the most favored of current trending meals in the world. It is simple, it&amp;rsquo;s quick, it tastes yummy. It&amp;rsquo;s appreciated by millions every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Prepare Speedy Sayap Ayam Bakar Bumbu Tauco (Kilat nan Lezat)</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/167-how-to-prepare-speedy-sayap-ayam-bakar-bumbu-tauco-kilat-nan-lezat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 06:23:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/167-how-to-prepare-speedy-sayap-ayam-bakar-bumbu-tauco-kilat-nan-lezat/</guid>
      <description>Sayap Ayam Bakar Bumbu Tauco (Kilat nan Lezat)
Hey everyone, hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a distinctive dish, sayap ayam bakar bumbu tauco (kilat nan lezat). One of my favorites. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Resep ramadhan kali ini yaitu Swike ayam atau ayam dengan bumbu tauco. aku menggunakan sayap ayam karena bagian sayap rasanya lebih gurih.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Any-night-of-the-week Tumis Ayam Jamur kuping (Rp 6.000)</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/117-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-tumis-ayam-jamur-kuping-rp-6000/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 02:12:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/117-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-tumis-ayam-jamur-kuping-rp-6000/</guid>
      <description>Tumis Ayam Jamur kuping (Rp 6.000)
Hey everyone, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an incredible day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a distinctive dish, tumis ayam jamur kuping (rp 6.000). One of my favorites. This time, I am going to make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Tumis Ayam Jamur kuping (Rp 6.000) is one of the most popular of recent trending meals on earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps to Prepare Ultimate Ayam Kampung Masak Santan</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/94-steps-to-prepare-ultimate-ayam-kampung-masak-santan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 15:09:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/94-steps-to-prepare-ultimate-ayam-kampung-masak-santan/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Kampung Masak Santan
Hey everyone, it is me again, Dan, welcome to my recipe page. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a special dish, ayam kampung masak santan. One of my favorites. For mine, I will make it a little bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Inilah satu alternatif sehat daripada tongseng pada umumnya. Versi sehat sebuah masakan biasanya bisa dicapai dengan mengganti beberapa elemen di dalamnya.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Make Perfect Gyoza Ayam</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/176-step-by-step-guide-to-make-perfect-gyoza-ayam/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 23:21:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/176-step-by-step-guide-to-make-perfect-gyoza-ayam/</guid>
      <description>Gyoza Ayam
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s me again, Dan, welcome to my recipe site. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a distinctive dish, gyoza ayam. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Hi Foodies, di episode kali ini kokiku.tv dengan Mommy Putri Wong akan share resep Gyoza Ayam yang mudah dan praktis. Tidak sabar untuk mencoba cemilan ini?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Langkah Mudah untuk Menyiapkan Setup roti coklat keju Anti Gagal</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/0-langkah-mudah-untuk-menyiapkan-setup-roti-coklat-keju-anti-gagal/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 04:29:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/0-langkah-mudah-untuk-menyiapkan-setup-roti-coklat-keju-anti-gagal/</guid>
      <description>Setup roti coklat keju
Lagi mencari inspirasi resep setup roti coklat keju yang unik? Cara membuatnya memang tidak terlalu sulit namun tidak gampang juga. Kalau keliru mengolah maka hasilnya akan hambar dan justru cenderung tidak enak. Padahal setup roti coklat keju yang enak selayaknya memiliki aroma dan cita rasa yang mampu memancing selera kita.
Lihat juga resep Setup roti tawar nigmat enak lainnya. Ada banyak varian setup roti yang bisa dibuat sendiri.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Perfect Ayam geprek runahan</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/119-recipe-of-perfect-ayam-geprek-runahan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 04:20:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/119-recipe-of-perfect-ayam-geprek-runahan/</guid>
      <description>Ayam geprek runahan
Hello everybody, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an incredible day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a distinctive dish, ayam geprek runahan. One of my favorites. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Resep Ayam Geprek Rumahan - Enak, gurih dan pedas, itulah hal pertamakali yang akan anda rasakan saat menikmati ayam geprek. Sajian ini cocok untuk teman makan siang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easiest Way to Make Perfect Ayam bakar bumbu rujak</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/14-easiest-way-to-make-perfect-ayam-bakar-bumbu-rujak/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 20:14:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/14-easiest-way-to-make-perfect-ayam-bakar-bumbu-rujak/</guid>
      <description>Ayam bakar bumbu rujak
Hey everyone, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an incredible day today. Today, I will show you a way to make a special dish, ayam bakar bumbu rujak. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I am going to make it a little bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Ayam dengan kuah bumbu rujak yang kental mungkin sudah pernah Anda coba. Bagaimana dengan ayam bakar dengan bumbu rujak?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Prepare Ultimate Sempol Ayam Kenyul</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/71-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-ultimate-sempol-ayam-kenyul/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 00:27:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/71-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-ultimate-sempol-ayam-kenyul/</guid>
      <description>Sempol Ayam Kenyul
Hello everybody, hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a special dish, sempol ayam kenyul. One of my favorites. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Hallo semuanya, jumpa lagi di Channel YouTube DAPUR SYUKASYUKA. Kudapan praktis ini terbuat dari campuran ayam, tepung tapioka, telur, dan berbagai bumbu lalu digoreng!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Prepare Speedy Sate Ayam Madura</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/102-how-to-prepare-speedy-sate-ayam-madura/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 00:02:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/102-how-to-prepare-speedy-sate-ayam-madura/</guid>
      <description>Sate Ayam Madura
Hello everybody, hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a special dish, sate ayam madura. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I am going to make it a bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Sebut saja sate padang, sate tegal, sate blora, sate maranggi, sate ponorogo, dan sate madura ini. Sate madura memiliki potongan daging ayam lebih kecil dibandingkan sate lainnya.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Any-night-of-the-week Tongseng ayam</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/59-how-to-make-any-night-of-the-week-tongseng-ayam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 10:45:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/59-how-to-make-any-night-of-the-week-tongseng-ayam/</guid>
      <description>Tongseng ayam
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s Brad, welcome to my recipe page. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a special dish, tongseng ayam. One of my favorites. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Tongseng ayam is one of the most popular of current trending meals in the world. It&amp;rsquo;s simple, it&amp;rsquo;s quick, it tastes delicious. It&amp;rsquo;s enjoyed by millions daily. Tongseng ayam is something that I have loved my whole life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Perfect 107. Sosis Tanpa Ayam (Sosis Kere)</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/24-how-to-make-perfect-107-sosis-tanpa-ayam-sosis-kere/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 21:09:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/24-how-to-make-perfect-107-sosis-tanpa-ayam-sosis-kere/</guid>
      <description>107. Sosis Tanpa Ayam (Sosis Kere)
Hey everyone, I hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a special dish, 107. sosis tanpa ayam (sosis kere). It is one of my favorites. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Sosis Tanpa Ayam (Sosis Kere) is one of the most popular of recent trending meals in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Make Homemade Ayam Pop Ala Rumahan Anti Ribet</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/147-step-by-step-guide-to-make-homemade-ayam-pop-ala-rumahan-anti-ribet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 11:21:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/147-step-by-step-guide-to-make-homemade-ayam-pop-ala-rumahan-anti-ribet/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Pop Ala Rumahan Anti Ribet
Hey everyone, hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an amazing day today. Today, I will show you a way to make a distinctive dish, ayam pop ala rumahan anti ribet. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Ayam Pop Ala Rumahan Anti Ribet is one of the most well liked of current trending meals in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Any-night-of-the-week Sate kulit ayam ala² angkringan</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/80-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-sate-kulit-ayam-ala-angkringan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 21:21:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/80-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-sate-kulit-ayam-ala-angkringan/</guid>
      <description>Sate kulit ayam ala² angkringan
Hello everybody, it is Jim, welcome to my recipe site. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a special dish, sate kulit ayam ala² angkringan. One of my favorites. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Kreasi resep simple masakan rumahan khas Indonesia adalah resep masakan rumahan favorit dan menu praktis sehari hari. Pernah membuat sate kulit ayam tapi gagal seperti terasa amis dan lembek?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Prepare Ultimate Ayam Saus Mentega Kecap</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/2-how-to-prepare-ultimate-ayam-saus-mentega-kecap/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 15:46:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/2-how-to-prepare-ultimate-ayam-saus-mentega-kecap/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Saus Mentega Kecap
Hello everybody, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an amazing day today. Today, I will show you a way to make a special dish, ayam saus mentega kecap. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I will make it a bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Ayam kecap mentega ini juga bisa dimasak sendiri di rumah lho. Bahkan banyak ibu rumah tangga menjadikan ayam kecap sebagai menu andalan untuk keluarga.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Super Quick Homemade Tongseng Ayam Bening</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/132-recipe-of-super-quick-homemade-tongseng-ayam-bening/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 15:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/132-recipe-of-super-quick-homemade-tongseng-ayam-bening/</guid>
      <description>Tongseng Ayam Bening
Hello everybody, it is me again, Dan, welcome to my recipe site. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a special dish, tongseng ayam bening. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I am going to make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Tongseng Ayam Bening is one of the most favored of recent trending meals on earth. It is simple, it is quick, it tastes delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Speedy Ayam kecap saus tiram👍🍅</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/93-how-to-make-speedy-ayam-kecap-saus-tiram/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 20:24:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/93-how-to-make-speedy-ayam-kecap-saus-tiram/</guid>
      <description>Ayam kecap saus tiram👍🍅
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s Brad, welcome to our recipe page. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a distinctive dish, ayam kecap saus tiram👍🍅. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I will make it a bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Bahan: Daging ayam Jahe Bawang bombay Cabe merah Kecap manis Saus tiram Penyedap rasa Minyak wijen Air secukupnya. Seperti kita tahu, saus tiram mampu &#39;menyulap&#39; sajian apapun jadi gurih dan lezat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Ultimate Ayam kecap Telur puyuh</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/34-recipe-of-ultimate-ayam-kecap-telur-puyuh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 14:58:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/34-recipe-of-ultimate-ayam-kecap-telur-puyuh/</guid>
      <description>Ayam kecap Telur puyuh
Hello everybody, hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an incredible day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a special dish, ayam kecap telur puyuh. It is one of my favorites. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Ayam kecap Telur puyuh is one of the most favored of current trending meals on earth. It&amp;rsquo;s appreciated by millions daily. It is simple, it is fast, it tastes delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Make Quick Tim Hati Ayam dan Kacang Polong</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/121-step-by-step-guide-to-make-quick-tim-hati-ayam-dan-kacang-polong/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 13:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/121-step-by-step-guide-to-make-quick-tim-hati-ayam-dan-kacang-polong/</guid>
      <description>Tim Hati Ayam dan Kacang Polong
Hello everybody, hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a special dish, tim hati ayam dan kacang polong. One of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I will make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Tim Hati Ayam dan Kacang Polong is one of the most favored of current trending meals on earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Prepare Speedy Ayam Popcorn Goreng Bawang</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/69-simple-way-to-prepare-speedy-ayam-popcorn-goreng-bawang/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 09:11:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/69-simple-way-to-prepare-speedy-ayam-popcorn-goreng-bawang/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Popcorn Goreng Bawang
Hey everyone, hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an incredible day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a distinctive dish, ayam popcorn goreng bawang. One of my favorites food recipes. This time, I will make it a little bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Maka dari itu, ayam popcorn selalu jadi andalan untuk camilan, bekal, ataupun lauk di rumah. Kini, menu ini sudah jadi kekinian karena dikreasikan dengan aneka topping/taburan seperti saus keju, saus bbq, atau bubuk cabai, sehingga disukai semua usia dan kalangan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Favorite Ayam Ungkep Praktis</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/166-recipe-of-favorite-ayam-ungkep-praktis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 03:06:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/166-recipe-of-favorite-ayam-ungkep-praktis/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Ungkep Praktis
Hello everybody, I hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a special dish, ayam ungkep praktis. One of my favorites. For mine, I will make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Ayam Ungkep Praktis is one of the most well liked of recent trending meals in the world. It&amp;rsquo;s simple, it is quick, it tastes yummy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Super Quick Homemade Ayam Tempe Pedas (Tanpa Minyak)</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/44-recipe-of-super-quick-homemade-ayam-tempe-pedas-tanpa-minyak/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 22:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/44-recipe-of-super-quick-homemade-ayam-tempe-pedas-tanpa-minyak/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Tempe Pedas (Tanpa Minyak)
Hey everyone, it is me again, Dan, welcome to my recipe site. Today, I will show you a way to make a distinctive dish, ayam tempe pedas (tanpa minyak). It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Ini dia resep ayam goreng air fryer yang lezatos mirip digoreng pake minyak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Any-night-of-the-week SOP ayam ala rumahan</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/64-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-sop-ayam-ala-rumahan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 19:35:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/64-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-sop-ayam-ala-rumahan/</guid>
      <description>SOP ayam ala rumahan
Hey everyone, I hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a distinctive dish, sop ayam ala rumahan. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
SOP ayam ala rumahan is one of the most well liked of current trending foods on earth. It is easy, it&amp;rsquo;s quick, it tastes yummy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Favorite Ayam Tinoransak Khas Manado</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/182-how-to-make-favorite-ayam-tinoransak-khas-manado/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 20:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/182-how-to-make-favorite-ayam-tinoransak-khas-manado/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Tinoransak Khas Manado
Hey everyone, I hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, I will show you a way to make a distinctive dish, ayam tinoransak khas manado. One of my favorites. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Ayam Tinoransak Khas Manado is one of the most favored of current trending meals on earth. It is simple, it is fast, it tastes yummy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Prepare Perfect Ayam bakar rosmary</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/97-simple-way-to-prepare-perfect-ayam-bakar-rosmary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 04:34:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/97-simple-way-to-prepare-perfect-ayam-bakar-rosmary/</guid>
      <description>Ayam bakar rosmary
Hey everyone, it is me, Dave, welcome to my recipe page. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a special dish, ayam bakar rosmary. It is one of my favorites. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Ayam bakar rosmary is one of the most favored of recent trending meals in the world. It&amp;rsquo;s simple, it&amp;rsquo;s fast, it tastes delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps to Make Perfect Bubur ayam teri keju</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/21-steps-to-make-perfect-bubur-ayam-teri-keju/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 15:41:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/21-steps-to-make-perfect-bubur-ayam-teri-keju/</guid>
      <description>Bubur ayam teri keju
Hey everyone, hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, I will show you a way to make a special dish, bubur ayam teri keju. One of my favorites food recipes. This time, I will make it a little bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Bubur ayam yang satu ini unik dan pastinya enak Berbagai macam pilihan menu bubur ada disini Bubur ini juga menggunakan cakwe dan chestik Lalu bisa di.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Speedy Ayam Betutu J.U.A.R.A</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/135-recipe-of-speedy-ayam-betutu-juara/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 14:37:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/135-recipe-of-speedy-ayam-betutu-juara/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Betutu J.U.A.R.A
Hello everybody, hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a special dish, ayam betutu j.u.a.r.a. One of my favorites. This time, I am going to make it a little bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Ayam Betutu J.U.A.R.A is one of the most favored of current trending meals in the world. It&amp;rsquo;s enjoyed by millions daily. It is easy, it is fast, it tastes yummy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Perfect Steak ayam rumahan saus keju sederhana</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/88-recipe-of-perfect-steak-ayam-rumahan-saus-keju-sederhana/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 20:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/88-recipe-of-perfect-steak-ayam-rumahan-saus-keju-sederhana/</guid>
      <description>Steak ayam rumahan saus keju sederhana
Hello everybody, hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a distinctive dish, steak ayam rumahan saus keju sederhana. One of my favorites. This time, I am going to make it a little bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Steak ayam saus jamur. foto: Instagram/@dapurfoody. Steak Ayam Rumahan yg Rasanya Seperti Warung Steak. • chicken katsu renyah dengan saus asam manis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cara Gampang Membuat Bola Bola Coklat Daur Ulang yang Enak</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/5-cara-gampang-membuat-bola-bola-coklat-daur-ulang-yang-enak/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 11:53:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/5-cara-gampang-membuat-bola-bola-coklat-daur-ulang-yang-enak/</guid>
      <description>Bola Bola Coklat Daur Ulang
Anda sedang mencari inspirasi resep bola bola coklat daur ulang yang unik? Cara menyiapkannya memang tidak susah dan tidak juga mudah. Jika keliru mengolah maka hasilnya tidak akan memuaskan dan bahkan tidak sedap. Padahal bola bola coklat daur ulang yang enak harusnya sih memiliki aroma dan cita rasa yang mampu memancing selera kita.
Kreasi Daur Ulang - Barang-barang daur ulang seperti botol bekas, kertas, kaleng, CD, dan Kepala kumbang dibuat dari bola pingpong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Prepare Award-winning Bubur Ayam</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/53-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-award-winning-bubur-ayam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 11:41:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/53-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-award-winning-bubur-ayam/</guid>
      <description>Bubur Ayam
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s Brad, welcome to my recipe page. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a distinctive dish, bubur ayam. One of my favorites. For mine, I will make it a little bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Bubur ayam (Indonesian for &amp;quot;chicken congee&amp;quot;) is a Chinese Indonesian chicken congee. It is rice congee with shredded chicken meat served with some condiments, such as chopped scallion, crispy fried shallot, celery, tongcay (preserved salted vegetables), fried soybean, Chinese crullers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Quick Ikan asin bulu ayam cabe ijo</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/142-recipe-of-quick-ikan-asin-bulu-ayam-cabe-ijo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 00:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/142-recipe-of-quick-ikan-asin-bulu-ayam-cabe-ijo/</guid>
      <description>Ikan asin bulu ayam cabe ijo
Hello everybody, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an incredible day today. Today, I will show you a way to make a special dish, ikan asin bulu ayam cabe ijo. It is one of my favorites. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Ikan asin bulu ayam cabe ijo is one of the most favored of recent trending meals in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easiest Way to Make Perfect 🍗Ayam goreng dg tepung bbq🍄</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/17-easiest-way-to-make-perfect-ayam-goreng-dg-tepung-bbq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 21:57:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/17-easiest-way-to-make-perfect-ayam-goreng-dg-tepung-bbq/</guid>
      <description>🍗Ayam goreng dg tepung bbq🍄
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s Louise, welcome to our recipe page. Today, I will show you a way to make a special dish, 🍗ayam goreng dg tepung bbq🍄. One of my favorites. For mine, I will make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Akhirnya kali ini kita bikin video perdana masak loh! WOOHOO~ Masakan perdana kita adalah CHICKEN WINGS BBQ SAUCE dengan. Ayam goreng tepung crispy ini proses pembuatannya agak sedikit rumit, sedikit berbeda dengan proses pembuatan ayam goreng bumbu kuning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Prepare Speedy Ayam Saus Plum</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/85-how-to-prepare-speedy-ayam-saus-plum/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 06:59:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/85-how-to-prepare-speedy-ayam-saus-plum/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Saus Plum
Hey everyone, it is me again, Dan, welcome to my recipe page. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a special dish, ayam saus plum. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Ayam Saus Plum is one of the most well liked of recent trending foods in the world. It is easy, it is fast, it tastes yummy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Make Favorite 528.Ayam Kentang Panggang</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/19-step-by-step-guide-to-make-favorite-528ayam-kentang-panggang/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 10:04:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/19-step-by-step-guide-to-make-favorite-528ayam-kentang-panggang/</guid>
      <description>528.Ayam Kentang Panggang
Hello everybody, hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an incredible day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a special dish, 528.ayam kentang panggang. It is one of my favorites. For mine, I will make it a little bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Sudah olahraga tiap hari tapi nggak berhasil menurunkan berat badan? Tapi bukan kentang panggang biasa, kami menyebutnya kentang panggang spesial dan punya rasa yang Endeus dari biasanya.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Make Favorite Ayam kecap cabe ijo 🐔</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/72-step-by-step-guide-to-make-favorite-ayam-kecap-cabe-ijo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 04:24:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/72-step-by-step-guide-to-make-favorite-ayam-kecap-cabe-ijo/</guid>
      <description>Ayam kecap cabe ijo 🐔
Hello everybody, it is me, Dave, welcome to our recipe site. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a special dish, ayam kecap cabe ijo 🐔. It is one of my favorites. This time, I will make it a bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Ayam kecap cabe ijo 🐔 is one of the most favored of recent trending meals on earth. It is appreciated by millions daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Any-night-of-the-week Ayam &amp;amp;amp; Telur Bumbu Bali</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/43-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-ayam-and-amp-telur-bumbu-bali/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 08:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/43-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-ayam-and-amp-telur-bumbu-bali/</guid>
      <description>Ayam &amp;amp;amp; Telur Bumbu Bali
Hello everybody, it is Brad, welcome to our recipe site. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a special dish, ayam &amp;amp; telur bumbu bali. One of my favorites. This time, I am going to make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Ayam features at a glance: RIB (RenderMan Interface Bytestream) export and. From Proto-Philippine *qayam, from Proto-Malayo-Polynesian *qayam. ayam. dog. From Proto-Philippine *qayam, from Proto-Malayo-Polynesian *qayam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Ultimate Ayam kecap</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/1-recipe-of-ultimate-ayam-kecap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 04:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/1-recipe-of-ultimate-ayam-kecap/</guid>
      <description>Ayam kecap
Hello everybody, it is John, welcome to our recipe page. Today, I will show you a way to make a distinctive dish, ayam kecap. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Menu ayam kecap jadi andalan kesukaan keluarga Indonesia. Proses pembakaran ayam bakar juga membuat kulit ayam terkaramelisasi oleh kecap. Lihat juga resep Ayam Kecap Sunda enak lainnya.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Quick 17. Tahu Walik Ayam</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/10-recipe-of-quick-17-tahu-walik-ayam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 20:39:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/10-recipe-of-quick-17-tahu-walik-ayam/</guid>
      <description>17. Tahu Walik Ayam
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s me again, Dan, welcome to my recipe site. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a special dish, 17. tahu walik ayam. It is one of my favorites. This time, I am going to make it a little bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Tahu Walik Ayam is one of the most favored of current trending meals on earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Perfect Soto ayam</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/35-recipe-of-perfect-soto-ayam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 23:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/35-recipe-of-perfect-soto-ayam/</guid>
      <description>Soto ayam
Hello everybody, hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an amazing day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a distinctive dish, soto ayam. One of my favorites. This time, I will make it a bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Lihat juga resep Soto Ayam/Ceker plus Kentang Crispy enak lainnya. Soto ayam merupakan satu dari ratusan ribu kuliner yang ada di Indonesia. Pada dasarnya soto ayam merupakan makanan yang berkuah kuning dengan suwiran ayam di dalamnya.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Favorite Ayam rica-rica</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/87-recipe-of-favorite-ayam-rica-rica/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 00:01:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/87-recipe-of-favorite-ayam-rica-rica/</guid>
      <description>Ayam rica-rica
Hello everybody, hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an incredible day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a distinctive dish, ayam rica-rica. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I am going to make it a little bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Ayam rica-rica is one of the most popular of current trending meals on earth. It is easy, it is quick, it tastes yummy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Ultimate 073. Soto Ayam Alaku</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/146-recipe-of-ultimate-073-soto-ayam-alaku/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 11:35:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/146-recipe-of-ultimate-073-soto-ayam-alaku/</guid>
      <description>073. Soto Ayam Alaku
Hey everyone, hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an incredible day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a distinctive dish, 073. soto ayam alaku. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I am going to make it a bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Kalo untuk balita, wortelnya bisa dihaluskan bersama ayam ya. Lihat juga resep Soto Ayam/Ceker plus Kentang Crispy enak lainnya.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Perfect Soto Ayam Santan</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/129-recipe-of-perfect-soto-ayam-santan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/129-recipe-of-perfect-soto-ayam-santan/</guid>
      <description>Soto Ayam Santan
Hello everybody, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an incredible day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a distinctive dish, soto ayam santan. One of my favorites. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Soto ayam santan ala resto. foto: Instagram/@hennysgalley. Seperti soto yang terdapat di Jawa, soto Medan juga menggunakan daging ayam sebagai bahan Bedanya, soto Medan menggunakan santan sehingga tekstur kuahnya lebih kental dan berwarna.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Speedy Ayam Masak Mentega Kecap</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/107-how-to-make-speedy-ayam-masak-mentega-kecap/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 16:50:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/107-how-to-make-speedy-ayam-masak-mentega-kecap/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Masak Mentega Kecap
Hello everybody, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an amazing day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a distinctive dish, ayam masak mentega kecap. It is one of my favorites. For mine, I am going to make it a little bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Ayam Masak Mentega Kecap is one of the most well liked of current trending meals on earth. It&amp;rsquo;s easy, it&amp;rsquo;s quick, it tastes yummy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Prepare Speedy #101 Ayam Teriyaki</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/15-how-to-prepare-speedy-101-ayam-teriyaki/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 12:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/15-how-to-prepare-speedy-101-ayam-teriyaki/</guid>
      <description>#101 Ayam Teriyaki
Hey everyone, I hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a distinctive dish, #101 ayam teriyaki. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
#101 Ayam Teriyaki is one of the most popular of current trending meals on earth. It&amp;rsquo;s appreciated by millions daily. It&amp;rsquo;s easy, it&amp;rsquo;s fast, it tastes yummy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Prepare Any-night-of-the-week Bistik Ayam</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/100-how-to-prepare-any-night-of-the-week-bistik-ayam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 00:41:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/100-how-to-prepare-any-night-of-the-week-bistik-ayam/</guid>
      <description>Bistik Ayam
Hello everybody, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an amazing day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a special dish, bistik ayam. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I will make it a little bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Bistik disajikan dengan sedikit kuah berwarna gelap yang manis, ringan, dan segar. Lihat juga resep Bistik ayam maknyuss enak lainnya. Resep Bistik Ayam - Menu olahan ayam yang simpel dan pasti disukai anak-anak nih Bun &amp;quot;Bistik Ayam Goreng&amp;quot;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Perfect Sop Ayam Wortel KembangTahu</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/33-recipe-of-perfect-sop-ayam-wortel-kembangtahu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 07:54:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/33-recipe-of-perfect-sop-ayam-wortel-kembangtahu/</guid>
      <description>Sop Ayam Wortel KembangTahu
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s Drew, welcome to my recipe site. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a distinctive dish, sop ayam wortel kembangtahu. One of my favorites. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Cara membuat sop ayam wortel sederhana. gampang banget dan enak. Sop ayam merupakan salah satu jenis menu masakan yang banyak disukai oleh banyak orang. Cara membuat: Pertama, rendam tahu kembang dengan air panas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Homemade Bola - bola ayam tahu mantul</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/81-recipe-of-homemade-bola-bola-ayam-tahu-mantul/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 01:44:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/81-recipe-of-homemade-bola-bola-ayam-tahu-mantul/</guid>
      <description>Bola - bola ayam tahu mantul
Hey everyone, hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an amazing day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a special dish, bola - bola ayam tahu mantul. One of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I am going to make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Bola - bola ayam tahu mantul is one of the most well liked of current trending meals on earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps to Make Super Quick Homemade Sate Ayam almunium foil Teflon</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/30-steps-to-make-super-quick-homemade-sate-ayam-almunium-foil-teflon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 01:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/30-steps-to-make-super-quick-homemade-sate-ayam-almunium-foil-teflon/</guid>
      <description>Sate Ayam almunium foil Teflon
Hello everybody, I hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a special dish, sate ayam almunium foil teflon. One of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I am going to make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Sate Ayam almunium foil Teflon is one of the most well liked of recent trending foods on earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Any-night-of-the-week Ayam Saos inggirs</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/67-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-ayam-saos-inggirs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 18:54:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/67-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-ayam-saos-inggirs/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Saos inggirs
Hello everybody, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an incredible day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a special dish, ayam saos inggirs. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I will make it a little bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Resep ayam saus inggris enak ala resto. Resep Ayam Saus Inggris Lezat dan Gampang dibuat. AYAM SAUS INGGRIS please follow instagram YUMI ELLEN wajib coba resep saus inggris enak banget dan gampang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Perfect Kare Ayam, Tahu dan Sayur</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/159-recipe-of-perfect-kare-ayam-tahu-dan-sayur/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 17:53:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/159-recipe-of-perfect-kare-ayam-tahu-dan-sayur/</guid>
      <description>Kare Ayam, Tahu dan Sayur
Hello everybody, hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a distinctive dish, kare ayam, tahu dan sayur. One of my favorites. This time, I am going to make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Kare Ayam, Tahu dan Sayur is one of the most favored of current trending meals in the world. It&amp;rsquo;s enjoyed by millions every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Ultimate Ayam Tinoransak Khas Manado</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/178-recipe-of-ultimate-ayam-tinoransak-khas-manado/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 16:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/178-recipe-of-ultimate-ayam-tinoransak-khas-manado/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Tinoransak Khas Manado
Hello everybody, hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a special dish, ayam tinoransak khas manado. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I am going to make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Ayam Tinoransak Khas Manado is one of the most well liked of recent trending foods on earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Speedy Ayam Goreng ala KFC</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/90-recipe-of-speedy-ayam-goreng-ala-kfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:57:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/90-recipe-of-speedy-ayam-goreng-ala-kfc/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Goreng ala KFC
Hey everyone, it is me, Dave, welcome to my recipe site. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a special dish, ayam goreng ala kfc. It is one of my favorites. For mine, I will make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Terlupa nak letak pada video dan malas nak. Untuk teman-teman yang mau membantu aku untuk membuat video youtube yang baru-baru lagi, kalian bisa support aku dengan cara donasi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Prepare Perfect 396. Ayam Goreng Sambel Jepun</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/36-how-to-prepare-perfect-396-ayam-goreng-sambel-jepun/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 20:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/36-how-to-prepare-perfect-396-ayam-goreng-sambel-jepun/</guid>
      <description>396. Ayam Goreng Sambel Jepun
Hey everyone, hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a distinctive dish, 396. ayam goreng sambel jepun. It is one of my favorites. This time, I will make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
#ayamgoreng #resep #masak Makan ayam goreng sambel ijo buatan sendiri Hey teman teman kali ini aku mau makan masakan sendiri nih yaitu makan ayam goreng.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Prepare Award-winning #101 Ayam Teriyaki</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/20-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-award-winning-101-ayam-teriyaki/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 10:02:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/20-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-award-winning-101-ayam-teriyaki/</guid>
      <description>#101 Ayam Teriyaki
Hello everybody, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an incredible day today. Today, I will show you a way to make a distinctive dish, #101 ayam teriyaki. It is one of my favorites. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
#101 Ayam Teriyaki is one of the most favored of recent trending meals on earth. It&amp;rsquo;s appreciated by millions daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Make Favorite Gyoza Ayam</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/180-simple-way-to-make-favorite-gyoza-ayam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 04:19:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/180-simple-way-to-make-favorite-gyoza-ayam/</guid>
      <description>Gyoza Ayam
Hey everyone, hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, I will show you a way to make a special dish, gyoza ayam. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I will make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Gyoza Ayam is one of the most popular of recent trending foods on earth. It&amp;rsquo;s enjoyed by millions daily. It&amp;rsquo;s simple, it is quick, it tastes delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps to Make Any-night-of-the-week Tonseng Ayam</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/70-steps-to-make-any-night-of-the-week-tonseng-ayam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 20:36:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/70-steps-to-make-any-night-of-the-week-tonseng-ayam/</guid>
      <description>Tonseng Ayam
Hey everyone, hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an amazing day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a distinctive dish, tonseng ayam. It is one of my favorites. This time, I am going to make it a little bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Tonseng Ayam is one of the most well liked of current trending meals on earth. It is appreciated by millions daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Ultimate Rice Bowl Ayam Lada Hitam</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/104-recipe-of-ultimate-rice-bowl-ayam-lada-hitam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 01:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/104-recipe-of-ultimate-rice-bowl-ayam-lada-hitam/</guid>
      <description>Rice Bowl Ayam Lada Hitam
Hello everybody, I hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a special dish, rice bowl ayam lada hitam. One of my favorites. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Rice Bowl Ayam Lada Hitam is one of the most well liked of current trending foods in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Make Award-winning Gulai Ayam Kemangi</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/153-step-by-step-guide-to-make-award-winning-gulai-ayam-kemangi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 12:39:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/153-step-by-step-guide-to-make-award-winning-gulai-ayam-kemangi/</guid>
      <description>Gulai Ayam Kemangi
Hey everyone, hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a special dish, gulai ayam kemangi. It is one of my favorites. This time, I am going to make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Learn how to make gulai ayam kampung with Chef Khder Mohsen Al-Issa. A dish of chicken cooked until tender in rich and creamy gulai sauce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Prepare Ultimate Ayam Suwir Balado</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/4-simple-way-to-prepare-ultimate-ayam-suwir-balado/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2020 19:47:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/4-simple-way-to-prepare-ultimate-ayam-suwir-balado/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Suwir Balado
Hey everyone, I hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a distinctive dish, ayam suwir balado. One of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I am going to make it a bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Ayam Suwir Balado is one of the most well liked of recent trending foods on earth. It is enjoyed by millions every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easiest Way to Prepare Favorite Ayam Bumbu Hitam Khas Madura</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/47-easiest-way-to-prepare-favorite-ayam-bumbu-hitam-khas-madura/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2020 14:05:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/47-easiest-way-to-prepare-favorite-ayam-bumbu-hitam-khas-madura/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Bumbu Hitam Khas Madura
Hello everybody, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an amazing day today. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a special dish, ayam bumbu hitam khas madura. One of my favorites. For mine, I am going to make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Ayam Bumbu Hitam Khas Madura is one of the most favored of current trending meals in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Prepare Super Quick Homemade Ayam Kecap (Sayap)</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/42-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-super-quick-homemade-ayam-kecap-sayap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2020 11:29:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/42-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-super-quick-homemade-ayam-kecap-sayap/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Kecap (Sayap)
Hello everybody, hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a special dish, ayam kecap (sayap). It is one of my favorites. For mine, I am going to make it a little bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Ayam Kecap (Sayap) is one of the most popular of recent trending meals in the world. It is enjoyed by millions every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resep Bomboloni Filling Cokelat, Bikin Ngiler</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/4-resep-bomboloni-filling-cokelat-bikin-ngiler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2020 10:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/4-resep-bomboloni-filling-cokelat-bikin-ngiler/</guid>
      <description>Bomboloni Filling Cokelat
Lagi mencari inspirasi resep bomboloni filling cokelat yang unik? Cara membuatnya memang tidak susah dan tidak juga mudah. Jika keliru mengolah maka hasilnya akan hambar dan bahkan tidak sedap. Padahal bomboloni filling cokelat yang enak selayaknya memiliki aroma dan cita rasa yang mampu memancing selera kita.
Banyak hal yang sedikit banyak berpengaruh terhadap kualitas rasa dari bomboloni filling cokelat, mulai dari jenis bahan, kemudian pemilihan bahan segar, hingga cara mengolah dan menghidangkannya.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps to Make Speedy Day. 158 Perkedel Tahu Ati Ayam (11 month&#43;)</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/160-steps-to-make-speedy-day-158-perkedel-tahu-ati-ayam-11-month/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2020 01:49:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/160-steps-to-make-speedy-day-158-perkedel-tahu-ati-ayam-11-month/</guid>
      <description>Day. 158 Perkedel Tahu Ati Ayam (11 month&amp;#43;)
Hey everyone, it is me again, Dan, welcome to my recipe page. Today, I will show you a way to make a distinctive dish, day. 158 perkedel tahu ati ayam (11 month+). One of my favorites food recipes. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Day. 158 Perkedel Tahu Ati Ayam (11 month+) is one of the most favored of current trending foods on earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Favorite Sop ayam kembang tahu</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/84-recipe-of-favorite-sop-ayam-kembang-tahu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 21:08:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/84-recipe-of-favorite-sop-ayam-kembang-tahu/</guid>
      <description>Sop ayam kembang tahu
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s John, welcome to our recipe page. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a special dish, sop ayam kembang tahu. One of my favorites. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Resep sop ayam - Ayam adalah lauk semua orang, karena memang ayam bisa diolah menjadi berbagai masakan dan tentunya disukai banyak orang. Jika sudah matang, Anda bisa mengangkatnya dan mematikan kompor, Anda bisa menyajikan sop ayam kembang tahu yang enak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Homemade Ayam Suwir Kemangi</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/5-how-to-make-homemade-ayam-suwir-kemangi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 16:46:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/5-how-to-make-homemade-ayam-suwir-kemangi/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Suwir Kemangi
Hey everyone, it is Drew, welcome to our recipe page. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a distinctive dish, ayam suwir kemangi. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Lihat juga resep Ayam suwir pedas kemangi enak lainnya. Nasi Bakar Ayam Suwir Kemangi siap disajikan. Daging ayam tersebut direbus, kemudian disuwir-suwir agar bentuknya menjadi serat-serat daging yang terpisah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Super Quick Homemade Ayam Crispy Saus Szechuan</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/50-recipe-of-super-quick-homemade-ayam-crispy-saus-szechuan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 13:37:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/50-recipe-of-super-quick-homemade-ayam-crispy-saus-szechuan/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Crispy Saus Szechuan
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s me, Dave, welcome to my recipe site. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a special dish, ayam crispy saus szechuan. It is one of my favorites. For mine, I will make it a little bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Ayam Crispy Saus Szechuan is one of the most popular of current trending meals on earth. It is simple, it is fast, it tastes yummy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Homemade Bola - bola ayam tahu mantul</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/74-recipe-of-homemade-bola-bola-ayam-tahu-mantul/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2020 11:12:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/74-recipe-of-homemade-bola-bola-ayam-tahu-mantul/</guid>
      <description>Bola - bola ayam tahu mantul
Hello everybody, it is me, Dave, welcome to our recipe page. Today, I will show you a way to make a distinctive dish, bola - bola ayam tahu mantul. One of my favorites. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Ayam bakar balado tahu tempe balado mantul. Live streaming sepak bola hari ini. *Silakan refresh atau hapus cache browser anda, untuk menampilkan Jadwal Live terbaru.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Any-night-of-the-week Burger Ayam Labu Kuning</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/122-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-burger-ayam-labu-kuning/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2020 20:34:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/122-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-burger-ayam-labu-kuning/</guid>
      <description>Burger Ayam Labu Kuning
Hey everyone, hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, I will show you a way to make a special dish, burger ayam labu kuning. One of my favorites food recipes. This time, I am going to make it a little bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Bukan Bubur Ayam Biasa, Bubur Ayam Labu Kuning Juga bisa jadi IDE JUALAN BURGER lho. Murah dan sehat pastinya, tanpa tambahan MSG dan bahan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Super Quick Homemade Ayam Pedas Manis</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/11-recipe-of-super-quick-homemade-ayam-pedas-manis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 22:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/11-recipe-of-super-quick-homemade-ayam-pedas-manis/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Pedas Manis
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s Brad, welcome to my recipe page. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a special dish, ayam pedas manis. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I will make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Ayam Pedas Manis is one of the most favored of recent trending foods on earth. It is enjoyed by millions every day. It&amp;rsquo;s easy, it is quick, it tastes yummy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Super Quick Homemade Ayam Goreng Oregano</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/12-recipe-of-super-quick-homemade-ayam-goreng-oregano/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 05:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/12-recipe-of-super-quick-homemade-ayam-goreng-oregano/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Goreng Oregano
Hey everyone, it is Drew, welcome to my recipe page. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a distinctive dish, ayam goreng oregano. One of my favorites food recipes. This time, I will make it a little bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Masak bersma Ank mengolah Dada Ayam menjadi lebih enak yaitu di Goreng kering biar lebih Gurih dan mantap. Lumuri ayam dengan air jeruk lemon Artikel ini telah tayang di Sajiansedap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Any-night-of-the-week Ayam Cabe</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/92-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-ayam-cabe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 04:52:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/92-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-ayam-cabe/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Cabe
Hello everybody, it is Drew, welcome to my recipe page. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a distinctive dish, ayam cabe. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I am going to make it a little bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Ungkep ayam di atas kompor: campurkan ayam, bumbu ungkep, bumbu halus, daun jeruk, dan air. #ayamcabeijo #masakansehari-hari assalamualaikum ketemu lagi,semoga kita smua dalam keadaan sehat lahir dan batin kali ini saya mu share resep ayam cabe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Make Any-night-of-the-week Ayam Bakso Lada hitam</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/57-simple-way-to-make-any-night-of-the-week-ayam-bakso-lada-hitam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 22:57:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/57-simple-way-to-make-any-night-of-the-week-ayam-bakso-lada-hitam/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Bakso Lada hitam
Hey everyone, it is Jim, welcome to our recipe site. Today, I will show you a way to make a distinctive dish, ayam bakso lada hitam. One of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I am going to make it a little bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Ayam yang miliki rasa lada hitam dari butiran lada yang masih utuh sangat berbeda dengan lada yang sudah dihaluskan yang dijual di minimarket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Prepare Award-winning Ayam bacem goreng</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/41-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-award-winning-ayam-bacem-goreng/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 12:01:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/41-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-award-winning-ayam-bacem-goreng/</guid>
      <description>Ayam bacem goreng
Hey everyone, I hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a special dish, ayam bacem goreng. It is one of my favorites. For mine, I am going to make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Ayam goreng yang direbus bersama dengan bumbu-bumbu dan gula merah lalu digoreng, memiliki rasa gurih dan manis. Menu ayam bacem goreng sangat cocok.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Super Quick Homemade Day. 159 Nasi Sop dan Ati Ayam Goreng (11 month&#43;)</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/83-how-to-make-super-quick-homemade-day-159-nasi-sop-dan-ati-ayam-goreng-11-month/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 10:18:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/83-how-to-make-super-quick-homemade-day-159-nasi-sop-dan-ati-ayam-goreng-11-month/</guid>
      <description>Day. 159 Nasi Sop dan Ati Ayam Goreng (11 month&amp;#43;)
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s Brad, welcome to my recipe site. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a distinctive dish, day. 159 nasi sop dan ati ayam goreng (11 month+). One of my favorites. For mine, I will make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Penonton dan Subscriber chanel youtube Si Jum Dr. Cara membuat nasi goreng dengan bumbu sajiku nasi goreng rasa ayam Jangan lupa like comen dan subscribe ke chanel youtube aku.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Speedy Sate kulit ayam ala² angkringan</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/73-recipe-of-speedy-sate-kulit-ayam-ala-angkringan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 03:52:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/73-recipe-of-speedy-sate-kulit-ayam-ala-angkringan/</guid>
      <description>Sate kulit ayam ala² angkringan
Hey everyone, it is me again, Dan, welcome to our recipe page. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a special dish, sate kulit ayam ala² angkringan. One of my favorites. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Kreasi resep simple masakan rumahan khas Indonesia adalah resep masakan rumahan favorit dan menu praktis sehari hari.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps to Make Super Quick Homemade Ayam Lada Hitam</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/112-steps-to-make-super-quick-homemade-ayam-lada-hitam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 05:23:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/112-steps-to-make-super-quick-homemade-ayam-lada-hitam/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Lada Hitam
Hello everybody, I hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a special dish, ayam lada hitam. One of my favorites. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Ayam Lada Hitam is one of the most popular of current trending foods on earth. It&amp;rsquo;s enjoyed by millions daily. It is easy, it is fast, it tastes delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easiest Way to Make Perfect Nuget ayam udang mix sayur</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/185-easiest-way-to-make-perfect-nuget-ayam-udang-mix-sayur/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 12:24:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/185-easiest-way-to-make-perfect-nuget-ayam-udang-mix-sayur/</guid>
      <description>Nuget ayam udang mix sayur
Hello everybody, it is Drew, welcome to our recipe page. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a special dish, nuget ayam udang mix sayur. One of my favorites. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
NUGGET AYAM SAYUR ANTI GAGAL Anti gagal jika diikuti di setiap step by stepnya dengan seksama. Potong-potong wortel Chicken nugget / nuget ayam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps to Prepare Speedy Ayam suwir balado</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/25-steps-to-prepare-speedy-ayam-suwir-balado/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 04:36:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/25-steps-to-prepare-speedy-ayam-suwir-balado/</guid>
      <description>Ayam suwir balado
Hey everyone, hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a special dish, ayam suwir balado. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I am going to make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Bosen makan ayam goreng, yuk ayamnya kita suwir - suwir terus dimasak balado. Ayam suwir balado ala saya ini pedasnya cukup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Favorite 🍗Ayam goreng dg tepung bbq🍄</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/22-how-to-make-favorite-ayam-goreng-dg-tepung-bbq/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 09:35:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/22-how-to-make-favorite-ayam-goreng-dg-tepung-bbq/</guid>
      <description>🍗Ayam goreng dg tepung bbq🍄
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s Drew, welcome to our recipe site. Today, I will show you a way to make a special dish, 🍗ayam goreng dg tepung bbq🍄. One of my favorites. For mine, I will make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Akhirnya kali ini kita bikin video perdana masak loh! WOOHOO~ Masakan perdana kita adalah CHICKEN WINGS BBQ SAUCE dengan. Ayam goreng tepung crispy ini proses pembuatannya agak sedikit rumit, sedikit berbeda dengan proses pembuatan ayam goreng bumbu kuning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Any-night-of-the-week Ayam Bakar Pedas Diet (NO OIL, NO SUGAR, NO SANTAN)</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/37-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-ayam-bakar-pedas-diet-no-oil-no-sugar-no-santan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 11:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/37-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-ayam-bakar-pedas-diet-no-oil-no-sugar-no-santan/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Bakar Pedas Diet (NO OIL, NO SUGAR, NO SANTAN)
Hey everyone, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an amazing day today. Today, I will show you a way to make a distinctive dish, ayam bakar pedas diet (no oil, no sugar, no santan). One of my favorites. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Ayam Bakar Pedas Diet (NO OIL, NO SUGAR, NO SANTAN) is one of the most favored of recent trending meals in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps to Make Perfect Kuah Bakso Ayam Simple #24</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/123-steps-to-make-perfect-kuah-bakso-ayam-simple-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 20:54:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/123-steps-to-make-perfect-kuah-bakso-ayam-simple-24/</guid>
      <description>Kuah Bakso Ayam Simple #24
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s Brad, welcome to my recipe page. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a distinctive dish, kuah bakso ayam simple #24. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I will make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Kuah Bakso Ayam Simple #24 is one of the most popular of current trending foods in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Speedy Hati ayam wortel kecap</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/101-recipe-of-speedy-hati-ayam-wortel-kecap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 02:38:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/101-recipe-of-speedy-hati-ayam-wortel-kecap/</guid>
      <description>Hati ayam wortel kecap
Hey everyone, it is Jim, welcome to our recipe site. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a distinctive dish, hati ayam wortel kecap. It is one of my favorites. For mine, I will make it a little bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Hati ayam wortel kecap is one of the most favored of current trending meals in the world. It&amp;rsquo;s appreciated by millions daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cara Gampang Membuat Fudgy Melted Choco Brownies panggang premium Anti Gagal</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/9-cara-gampang-membuat-fudgy-melted-choco-brownies-panggang-premium-anti-gagal/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 03:20:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/9-cara-gampang-membuat-fudgy-melted-choco-brownies-panggang-premium-anti-gagal/</guid>
      <description>Fudgy Melted Choco Brownies panggang premium
Anda sedang mencari inspirasi resep fudgy melted choco brownies panggang premium yang unik? Cara membuatnya memang susah-susah gampang. Jika salah mengolah maka hasilnya akan hambar dan justru cenderung tidak enak. Padahal fudgy melted choco brownies panggang premium yang enak selayaknya mempunyai aroma dan cita rasa yang dapat memancing selera kita.
Ada beberapa hal yang sedikit banyak berpengaruh terhadap kualitas rasa dari fudgy melted choco brownies panggang premium, mulai dari jenis bahan, kemudian pemilihan bahan segar, hingga cara mengolah dan menyajikannya.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Prepare Speedy Kare Ayam</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/181-how-to-prepare-speedy-kare-ayam/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 08:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/181-how-to-prepare-speedy-kare-ayam/</guid>
      <description>Kare Ayam
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s Drew, welcome to our recipe site. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a distinctive dish, kare ayam. One of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I will make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Kare Ayam adalah masakan khas Jawa Timur. Bumbunya komplit sehingga menghasilkan Kare ayam yang rasanya sangat mantap tak ada bandingnya. Mendengarkan resep kare ayam bahan kare ayam cara membuat kare ayam Jawa Tengah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Any-night-of-the-week Nugget Ayam Homemade</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/149-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-nugget-ayam-homemade/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 22:54:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/149-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-nugget-ayam-homemade/</guid>
      <description>Nugget Ayam Homemade
Hey everyone, I hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a distinctive dish, nugget ayam homemade. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I am going to make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Video Cara Membuat nugget ayam Asahid dan Tehyung kali ini akan mempersembahkan resep cara membuat nugget ayam. Untuk Bahan Bahannya membuat nugget ayam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Any-night-of-the-week Soto Ayam Favorit</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/27-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-soto-ayam-favorit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 12:58:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/27-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-soto-ayam-favorit/</guid>
      <description>Soto Ayam Favorit
Hello everybody, hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an amazing day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a special dish, soto ayam favorit. One of my favorites. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Lihat juga resep Soto Ayam/Ceker plus Kentang Crispy enak lainnya. Soto Ayam Lamongan merupakan masakan nusantara yang sangat terkenal di seluruh pelosok negeri ini. Dengan rasa yang enak dan lezat tak heran jika soto Lamongan disukai banyak masyarakat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Make Award-winning Ayam Panggang Bumbu Rujak Rumahan</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/60-step-by-step-guide-to-make-award-winning-ayam-panggang-bumbu-rujak-rumahan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 07:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/60-step-by-step-guide-to-make-award-winning-ayam-panggang-bumbu-rujak-rumahan/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Panggang Bumbu Rujak Rumahan
Hey everyone, I hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a special dish, ayam panggang bumbu rujak rumahan. It is one of my favorites. This time, I am going to make it a little bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Ayam Panggang Bumbu Rujak Rumahan is one of the most favored of recent trending meals on earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Any-night-of-the-week Ayam Richesee Kw</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/32-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-ayam-richesee-kw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 16:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/32-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-ayam-richesee-kw/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Richesee Kw
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s Louise, welcome to my recipe site. Today, I will show you a way to make a special dish, ayam richesee kw. One of my favorites food recipes. This time, I will make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Ayam Richesee Kw is one of the most popular of recent trending meals on earth. It is enjoyed by millions daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Make Favorite Soto daging sapi dan ayam santan kuning 😂😍</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/63-step-by-step-guide-to-make-favorite-soto-daging-sapi-dan-ayam-santan-kuning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 06:19:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/63-step-by-step-guide-to-make-favorite-soto-daging-sapi-dan-ayam-santan-kuning/</guid>
      <description>Soto daging sapi dan ayam santan kuning 😂😍
Hey everyone, it is Brad, welcome to our recipe site. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a special dish, soto daging sapi dan ayam santan kuning 😂😍. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I will make it a little bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Soto daging sapi dan ayam santan kuning 😂😍 is one of the most popular of current trending meals on earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Super Quick Homemade Ayam Panggang Pedas Manis</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/86-recipe-of-super-quick-homemade-ayam-panggang-pedas-manis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 04:28:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/86-recipe-of-super-quick-homemade-ayam-panggang-pedas-manis/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Panggang Pedas Manis
Hello everybody, I hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an incredible day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a special dish, ayam panggang pedas manis. One of my favorites. For mine, I am going to make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Ayam Gulung Panggang Manis Pedas, merupakan resep unik yang menggunakan Kecap Bango Manis Pedas Gurih. Resep yang unik dan super spesial buat akhir pekan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Super Quick Homemade Oseng ayam</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/49-recipe-of-super-quick-homemade-oseng-ayam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 01:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/49-recipe-of-super-quick-homemade-oseng-ayam/</guid>
      <description>Oseng ayam
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s Jim, welcome to our recipe page. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a special dish, oseng ayam. One of my favorites. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Sambal baby cumi, oseng ayam + tempe , asmr indonesia ASMR adalah singkatan dari Autonomous Sensory Meridian Response. Lihat juga resep Oseng Ayam Pedas Daun Jeruk enak lainnya.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Favorite Ayam Bacem</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/58-recipe-of-favorite-ayam-bacem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 17:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/58-recipe-of-favorite-ayam-bacem/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Bacem
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s Brad, welcome to our recipe page. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a special dish, ayam bacem. One of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I will make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Ayam Bacem is one of the most popular of current trending foods on earth. It is easy, it is quick, it tastes delicious. It is appreciated by millions every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Make Favorite 🐔 Soto ayam special 🐣</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/62-step-by-step-guide-to-make-favorite-soto-ayam-special/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 12:12:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/62-step-by-step-guide-to-make-favorite-soto-ayam-special/</guid>
      <description>🐔 Soto ayam special 🐣
Hello everybody, hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a distinctive dish, 🐔 soto ayam special 🐣. One of my favorites. This time, I will make it a little bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
🐔 Soto ayam special 🐣 is one of the most favored of current trending foods in the world. It is simple, it is fast, it tastes yummy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Speedy Ayam kecap bumbu pedas</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/133-recipe-of-speedy-ayam-kecap-bumbu-pedas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 04:59:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/133-recipe-of-speedy-ayam-kecap-bumbu-pedas/</guid>
      <description>Ayam kecap bumbu pedas
Hey everyone, it is Brad, welcome to our recipe site. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a distinctive dish, ayam kecap bumbu pedas. One of my favorites. For mine, I will make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Ayam kecap bumbu pedas is one of the most well liked of current trending meals on earth. It&amp;rsquo;s enjoyed by millions every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Ultimate Soto Ayam</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/183-recipe-of-ultimate-soto-ayam/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 11:20:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/183-recipe-of-ultimate-soto-ayam/</guid>
      <description>Soto Ayam
Hello everybody, hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an amazing day today. Today, I will show you a way to make a special dish, soto ayam. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Soto Ayam is one of the most well liked of recent trending foods on earth. It is appreciated by millions every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Homemade Ayam Charsiu</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/116-recipe-of-homemade-ayam-charsiu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 18:51:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/116-recipe-of-homemade-ayam-charsiu/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Charsiu
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s me again, Dan, welcome to our recipe page. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a distinctive dish, ayam charsiu. It is one of my favorites. This time, I am going to make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Ayam Charsiu is one of the most favored of recent trending foods on earth. It is enjoyed by millions every day. It&amp;rsquo;s simple, it&amp;rsquo;s fast, it tastes yummy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Perfect Roti Sobek Kukus Isi Ayam Kecap</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/26-recipe-of-perfect-roti-sobek-kukus-isi-ayam-kecap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 05:24:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/26-recipe-of-perfect-roti-sobek-kukus-isi-ayam-kecap/</guid>
      <description>Roti Sobek Kukus Isi Ayam Kecap
Hey everyone, hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a special dish, roti sobek kukus isi ayam kecap. One of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I will make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Resep Roti Sobek Kukus Isi Sosis yang Enak dan Lembut, Wajib Coba! Mau buat roti sobek tapi enggak punya oven?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps to Make Speedy Kare Ayam</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/177-steps-to-make-speedy-kare-ayam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 05:18:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/177-steps-to-make-speedy-kare-ayam/</guid>
      <description>Kare Ayam
Hello everybody, hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a distinctive dish, kare ayam. One of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Kare Ayam is one of the most well liked of recent trending meals on earth. It is appreciated by millions every day. It&amp;rsquo;s simple, it&amp;rsquo;s fast, it tastes delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Super Quick Homemade Ayam cabe hijau kemangi</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/125-recipe-of-super-quick-homemade-ayam-cabe-hijau-kemangi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 12:33:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/125-recipe-of-super-quick-homemade-ayam-cabe-hijau-kemangi/</guid>
      <description>Ayam cabe hijau kemangi
Hey everyone, it is Brad, welcome to my recipe page. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a distinctive dish, ayam cabe hijau kemangi. It is one of my favorites. This time, I am going to make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Ayam cabe hijau kemangi is one of the most popular of current trending meals in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps to Make Quick Ayam geprek surabaya</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/175-steps-to-make-quick-ayam-geprek-surabaya/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 00:42:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/175-steps-to-make-quick-ayam-geprek-surabaya/</guid>
      <description>Ayam geprek surabaya
Hello everybody, hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an incredible day today. Today, I will show you a way to make a special dish, ayam geprek surabaya. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I am going to make it a bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Sebelum banyak restoran ayam geprek di Surabaya, Kakkk Ayam Geprek ini merupakan pelopor Di antara berbagai tempat makan ayam geprek yang buka di Surabaya, Gerobak Ayam Geprek ini.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Make Any-night-of-the-week Ayam geprek sambal tomat 🍅</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/126-step-by-step-guide-to-make-any-night-of-the-week-ayam-geprek-sambal-tomat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 14:20:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/126-step-by-step-guide-to-make-any-night-of-the-week-ayam-geprek-sambal-tomat/</guid>
      <description>Ayam geprek sambal tomat 🍅
Hello everybody, I hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, I will show you a way to make a special dish, ayam geprek sambal tomat 🍅. One of my favorites food recipes. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Ayam geprek sambal tomat 🍅 is one of the most well liked of current trending foods in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Ultimate Ayam rica-rica</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/79-recipe-of-ultimate-ayam-rica-rica/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 16:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/79-recipe-of-ultimate-ayam-rica-rica/</guid>
      <description>Ayam rica-rica
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s Drew, welcome to our recipe site. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a special dish, ayam rica-rica. It is one of my favorites. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Ayam rica-rica is one of the most popular of recent trending meals on earth. It&amp;rsquo;s easy, it is fast, it tastes yummy. It&amp;rsquo;s enjoyed by millions every day. They&amp;rsquo;re fine and they look fantastic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Homemade Ayam bakar areh(Klaten)</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/130-recipe-of-homemade-ayam-bakar-arehklaten/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 02:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/130-recipe-of-homemade-ayam-bakar-arehklaten/</guid>
      <description>Ayam bakar areh(Klaten)
Hello everybody, hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an amazing day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a distinctive dish, ayam bakar areh(klaten). It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Ayam bakar khas Klaten Jawa Tengah ini bukan hanya digemari warga lokal saja, bahkan setiap orang yang pernah mengunjungi Klaten dan mencicipinya pasti suka.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easiest Way to Prepare Speedy Bistik ayam dan telur</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/40-easiest-way-to-prepare-speedy-bistik-ayam-dan-telur/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 05:28:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/40-easiest-way-to-prepare-speedy-bistik-ayam-dan-telur/</guid>
      <description>Bistik ayam dan telur
Hey everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s Louise, welcome to my recipe site. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a distinctive dish, bistik ayam dan telur. It is one of my favorites. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Pasti ramai yang tertanya-tanya bagaimana telur bistik yang sedap dan manis di kedai dibuat? Lihat juga resep Bistik ayam maknyuss enak lainnya. Bistik disajikan dengan sedikit kuah berwarna gelap yang manis, ringan, dan segar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easiest Way to Prepare Any-night-of-the-week Ayam krispy saus asam manis simple</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/48-easiest-way-to-prepare-any-night-of-the-week-ayam-krispy-saus-asam-manis-simple/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 12:12:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/48-easiest-way-to-prepare-any-night-of-the-week-ayam-krispy-saus-asam-manis-simple/</guid>
      <description>Ayam krispy saus asam manis simple
Hey everyone, hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a distinctive dish, ayam krispy saus asam manis simple. One of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Kali ini aku memasak Ayam Crispy Saus Asam Manis. Masakan sederhana tapi enak dan lezat, bikin ketagihan loh gaes!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Ultimate Lumpia Ayam Sayur</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/172-recipe-of-ultimate-lumpia-ayam-sayur/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 11:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/172-recipe-of-ultimate-lumpia-ayam-sayur/</guid>
      <description>Lumpia Ayam Sayur
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s Louise, welcome to my recipe page. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a special dish, lumpia ayam sayur. It is one of my favorites. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Ngomongin tentang Semarang, apa nih yang paling bikin kamu kangen sama kota ini? Yang sukanya #JelajahKulinerNusantara di ibukota Jawa Tengah ini pasti. Resep &#39;lumpia sayur ayam&#39; paling teruji.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resep Strawberry Chocolate French Toast Roll yang Enak Banget</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/2-resep-strawberry-chocolate-french-toast-roll-yang-enak-banget/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 08:51:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/2-resep-strawberry-chocolate-french-toast-roll-yang-enak-banget/</guid>
      <description>Strawberry Chocolate French Toast Roll
Anda sedang mencari ide resep strawberry chocolate french toast roll yang unik? Cara membuatnya memang tidak terlalu sulit namun tidak gampang juga. Kalau keliru mengolah maka hasilnya akan hambar dan bahkan tidak sedap. Padahal strawberry chocolate french toast roll yang enak harusnya sih mempunyai aroma dan rasa yang mampu memancing selera kita.
Banyak hal yang sedikit banyak mempengaruhi kualitas rasa dari strawberry chocolate french toast roll, mulai dari jenis bahan, lalu pemilihan bahan segar, sampai cara membuat dan menyajikannya.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Langkah Mudah untuk Menyiapkan Selai Coklat homemade/ isi bomboloni Anti Gagal</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/7-langkah-mudah-untuk-menyiapkan-selai-coklat-homemade-isi-bomboloni-anti-gagal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 09:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/7-langkah-mudah-untuk-menyiapkan-selai-coklat-homemade-isi-bomboloni-anti-gagal/</guid>
      <description>Selai Coklat homemade/ isi bomboloni
Sedang mencari ide resep selai coklat homemade/ isi bomboloni yang unik? Cara membuatnya memang susah-susah gampang. Kalau salah mengolah maka hasilnya akan hambar dan justru cenderung tidak enak. Padahal selai coklat homemade/ isi bomboloni yang enak selayaknya memiliki aroma dan rasa yang bisa memancing selera kita.
Ada beberapa hal yang sedikit banyak berpengaruh terhadap kualitas rasa dari selai coklat homemade/ isi bomboloni, mulai dari jenis bahan, lalu pemilihan bahan segar, hingga cara mengolah dan menyajikannya.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps to Make Award-winning Soto Ayam</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/179-steps-to-make-award-winning-soto-ayam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 07:23:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/179-steps-to-make-award-winning-soto-ayam/</guid>
      <description>Soto Ayam
Hello everybody, hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an amazing day today. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a special dish, soto ayam. One of my favorites. For mine, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Soto Ayam is one of the most popular of recent trending foods in the world. It&amp;rsquo;s appreciated by millions daily. It&amp;rsquo;s simple, it is fast, it tastes yummy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Any-night-of-the-week Ayam goreng kremes</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/164-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-ayam-goreng-kremes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 23:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/164-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-ayam-goreng-kremes/</guid>
      <description>Ayam goreng kremes
Hello everybody, it is Louise, welcome to our recipe page. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a distinctive dish, ayam goreng kremes. One of my favorites. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Ayam goreng kremes is one of the most well liked of recent trending foods in the world. It&amp;rsquo;s appreciated by millions every day. It&amp;rsquo;s easy, it&amp;rsquo;s quick, it tastes delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Make Speedy Ayam Popcorn Gr Bawang</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/103-step-by-step-guide-to-make-speedy-ayam-popcorn-gr-bawang/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 11:10:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/103-step-by-step-guide-to-make-speedy-ayam-popcorn-gr-bawang/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Popcorn Gr Bawang
Hey everyone, hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an amazing day today. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a special dish, ayam popcorn gr bawang. One of my favorites. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Ayam popcorn sambal manis, hidangan yang mudah tapi gerenti sedap. Kita masak apa yang bisa kita masak dan kita makan apa yang bisa dimakan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Prepare Ultimate Ayam Kung Pao</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/158-simple-way-to-prepare-ultimate-ayam-kung-pao/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 10:24:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/158-simple-way-to-prepare-ultimate-ayam-kung-pao/</guid>
      <description>Ayam Kung Pao
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s Louise, welcome to our recipe page. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a special dish, ayam kung pao. One of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I am going to make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Ayam Kung Pao is one of the most popular of recent trending meals on earth. It is enjoyed by millions every day. It&amp;rsquo;s simple, it&amp;rsquo;s fast, it tastes yummy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Ultimate Ayam rica rica</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/138-recipe-of-ultimate-ayam-rica-rica/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 22:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/138-recipe-of-ultimate-ayam-rica-rica/</guid>
      <description>Ayam rica rica
Hello everybody, I hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, I will show you a way to make a distinctive dish, ayam rica rica. It is one of my favorites. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Inilah rahasia bumbu masakan ayam rica rica dan petunjuk cara membuat rica rica ayam. Resep ayam rica rica merupakan masakan selera pedas dari daerah manado.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bagaimana Membuat 27. Choco Dorayaki (Takaran Sendok), Menggugah Selera</title>
      <link>https://bibiresep.web.app/8-bagaimana-membuat-27-choco-dorayaki-takaran-sendok-menggugah-selera/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 23:04:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bibiresep.web.app/8-bagaimana-membuat-27-choco-dorayaki-takaran-sendok-menggugah-selera/</guid>
      <description>27. Choco Dorayaki (Takaran Sendok)
Sedang mencari inspirasi resep 27. choco dorayaki (takaran sendok) yang unik? Cara membuatnya memang tidak terlalu sulit namun tidak gampang juga. Jika keliru mengolah maka hasilnya akan hambar dan bahkan tidak sedap. Padahal 27. choco dorayaki (takaran sendok) yang enak selayaknya punya aroma dan cita rasa yang mampu memancing selera kita.
Banyak hal yang sedikit banyak mempengaruhi kualitas rasa dari 27. choco dorayaki (takaran sendok), mulai dari jenis bahan, kemudian pemilihan bahan segar sampai cara mengolah dan menghidangkannya.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
